Do something! God damn it!
Pull yourselves together and listen up!
When I give the sign,
just take three steps forward!
Go forward? Are you crazy?
We have to make them trip!
That's bullshit!
Let's give it a shot!
No, I can't do it!
If you can't, you'll die!
On the count of three! One!
Two!
Three!
Pull!
Pull…
No!
EPISODE 5
A FAIR WORLD
Hey.
Who are you praying to right now?
To God?
Do you think you're alive thanks to God?
You're still breathing
and moving that tongue of yours
thanks to that old man
and that guy over there who came up
with an awesome last-minute trick.
So if you're going to thank anyone,
thank them.
You poor lost sheep.
Can't you hear the cries of those
who were nailed to the cross today?
We lived to see another day
thanks to their blood and sacrifice.
On behalf of all us sinners,
I gave thanks to the Lord's decision
of their sacrifice
and said a prayer.
Bullshit.
You killed them yourself.
Do we all go to heaven
if we say a few prayers?
Shit, then I have to pray too.
Heavenly Father,
we worked together as a team today
to send many people to your side.
Please help us send
more people to your side from now on--
Be quiet.
Me?
Or that guy?
Both of you.
What's your name?
Why do you want to know?
To call you by your name, obviously.
Don't call me then.
You're so secretive.
Do me a favor.
Just leave me alone.
You're the one who talked to me first.
Did you see that bald guy wet his pants?
After that, all the kids behind him kept…
He's not breathing.
Go get the doctor.
I seriously thought
we were all going to die.
But once I laid back,
I really felt much more powerful.
"What is this? This works?"
Sir, how did you come up with that?
When I was young, I just--
You copied that from a movie, right?
What's that movie?
You know, the one that goes like this.
The Matrix.
Hey, did you only watch movies in Korea
instead of work?
And you, babe.
"Just take three steps forward!"
I mean, that was way too cool.
How did you come up with that
in that situation?
You said that was bullshit.
I did?
What bullshit are you saying?
You were crying,
"Are you crazy? That's bullshit!"
That's what you said.
Hey! Which country are you from?
Do you even have a visa?
You're an illegal alien, right?
Gosh. Look, boys.
Should we really
let this strange foreign guy
stay on our team? Should we?
I need to restructure this team
while I have the chance.
Who's the leader here?
Cool guy, are you the leader?
We don't have a leader.
We're all equal on this team.
Even better.
An egalitarian society!
Shit, it's totally different
from some damn thug
who runs everything as he wants
like he's the king.
But, why did you get kicked out, ma'am?
Babe.
Don't call me ma'am.
My name is Han Mi-nyeo.
Just call me Mi-nyeo.
And I wasn't kicked out.
I chose to leave the team.
Those thugs and I were
on completely different levels.
They only abandoned you,
then picked out able-bodied men.
Right before the game at that.
It's as if they knew what game
we were playing next.
Lights-out will be in 30 minutes.
Please get ready to sleep.
Another fight might break out tonight.
We should be prepared.
How so?
We have these women and an old man.
We're the weakest team here.
Let's pick a weak team
and attack them first.
The Lord's servant is more brutal than us.
We're all sinners already.
Our hands are drenched in blood.
Offense is the best form of defense.
Let's attack first.
During the fight last night,
do you know
how the man in front of me died?
Someone who he thought
was on his side broke his neck.
Do you all trust me?
I don't trust any of you.
All right.
We should focus on
protecting ourselves first.
Let's set up a barricade
before the lights go out.
It'll help to have some form of cover.
Hey, Mr. Ssangmun-dong.
You're trying so hard to stay alive.
But
do you think these will help?
It looks mighty drafty.
What about you?
Those scumbags on your so-called team.
Do you really trust them?
Try me.
Try it, bitch.
Go ahead. Bring it on.
If I were one of them,
once the fighting starts at night,
I'd wait for a chance to kill you first.
You're the strongest one after all.
How's that?
Boss.
Which team should we crush first?
Let's take the night off.
Why?
Let's cut down the numbers--
Let's just rest.
Okay.
Hey.
All of you, put those down
and get some rest.
Where's the doc?
He went out a moment ago
to use the restroom.
The lights will go out soon.
They won't attack us so easily,
but let's take turns
keeping watch just in case.
Let's do it in pairs.
There's a chance one may fall asleep
or side with another team to betray us.
I'll
go first.
Old people don't get very sleepy.
Sir,
how are we going to trust an old man
like you and sleep in peace?
I'll go first.
I'll join you.
I'm not sleepy right now.
Then I'll go next.
Wake me up when you get tired.
Then I'll join you,
if you're okay with it.
Let's do that.
The work schedule is done for today.
All workers, please return to your rooms.
All workers,
please return to your rooms immediately.
Have this.
I saved it from dinner earlier.
To give it to you, sir.
Why would you do that?
You saved my life today, sir.
I wanted to thank you.
There's no need to thank me.
I did it to save myself.
You gave me the bus fare too.
I should return the favor.
Happy?
Your name is Ali, right?
How old are you?
I'm 33 years old.
Then just call me Sang-woo.
May I do that,
Sang-woo?
How did you end up here?
I came to Korea to make money,
Sang-woo.
No, I don't mean Korea. Here.
This game.
I came because
I had no money.
Any family?
My mom, dad, and younger siblings
are back in Pakistan.
And my wife and baby are in Korea with me.
You have a kid?
How old?
A one-year-old son.
You must miss them.
I do.
How did you end up
here?
Because I had no money.
To make money.
Number 29,
what happened yesterday?
Why didn't you show up?
Sorry.
"Sorry"?
I stopped the others from killing you
because they can't trust you.
I owed it to you for saving my life
on our dive last time.
If you do that again, you're out.
Number 29. You're finally here.
I gave him a warning.
We couldn't make the delivery last night.
We can't let it slide with a warning!
Then you can deliver it yourself.
Do you think it's easy to find
divers like us in this place?
Make sure today's delivery
goes without a hitch.
What? You're not even done with one?
The doctor is
much slower than usual today.
Hey, quack. Hurry it up.
It's all in vain if the ship
leaves before we deliver.
Try doing this without getting
much sleep or decent food
while barely escaping death every day.
And so we tell you what the game is
and give you extra food
to make sure you don't die.
Gi-hun.
Sang-woo.
Let's switch.
Okay, sure.
Will you be okay?
What?
It looks like you had a nightmare.
No.
I'm fine.
Hey.
Why aren't you sleeping, Boss?
I can't seem to fall asleep.
I'm keeping everyone safe.
Don't worry and go to sleep.
I trust you, punk.
The doc still isn't back?
No.
It's weird. He's been gone far too long.
Hold it.
We're in a hurry.
Should I try working on those?
I think I can do it
if you teach me a few tricks.
Does it look easy
because I'm here like this?
I saw on the news that nurse aides
or office managers often perform surgery.
And some of them are better than doctors.
If you're that confident, do it yourself.
The quack who killed a man
by malpractice is still so proud.
If you're so good,
how'd you ruin the eyeballs last time?
Our buyers bashed me for it!
It was because that guy was still alive!
Everything was ruined
because he woke up and struggled!
We have no time for this.
The ship will arrive soon.
Gi-hun.
Hey.
What are you thinking about so deeply?
I thought you were sleeping
with your eyes open.
I was thinking about the past.
The past?
We once went on strike at my old company.
We set up a barricade like this.
What kind of company did you work for?
A car company.
What was the strike for?
They fired us because
they were financially troubled.
I'd worked there for over a decade.
It must've been tough.
My kid was about to be born,
and I had a million things to pay for.
They suddenly told us to leave,
so I had no alternative.
They ruined the company
and held us responsible.
It made me furious.
Just like now, my colleagues and I
took turns keeping watch at night
to occupy the factory.
Scared the police might
barge in any minute,
we trembled every night.
I remember. About ten years ago or so,
there was a big strike at a car company.
I think the news turned it
into a big story too.
Someone died there, right?
Yes.
Goodness.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't
have mentioned it.
Sir.
Are you okay?
-You're burning up.
-It's okay.
I nearly wet my pants that night.
I thought that thing was dead,
but it suddenly got up like a zombie,
and glared at me with one eye popping out.
I saw it in my dreams last night.
Everyone who failed Red Light, Green Light
was shot by a sniper rifle,
so we could hardly salvage anything.
I thought that zombie was decent
just by its looks.
I almost died delivering on that day,
but we didn't even get full price
because it only had one kidney.
Is it my fault
that the zombie had only one kidney?
Hopefully, this guy is all right.
Most of the people here either signed
away their bodies or are terminally ill.
I don't feel great about this.
Lie down.
Wait here.
We need to lower your fever.
Darn it.
Use this.
What happened…
to that zombie?
What do you think?
I hurriedly beat it to death
with that over there.
Why do you ask, though?
You saw it all.
What's wrong with you?
Don't you remember?
Back then,
I was a bit out of it.
You were out of it?
You even got rid of the body
with your own hands.
Number 29.
-You--
-This is my operating room!
Stop chitchatting and hold this properly!
Let me focus on my work!
If you don't, I'll cut through
his liver and kidneys with this!
Thank you.
Get some rest.
You need to get better
and play another game with us tomorrow.
You should go back to sleep.
I can do this alone.
We agreed to do it in pairs.
I'm already awake anyway.
Thanks
for the water.
It wasn't for free.
Pay me back tomorrow.
-Hurry.
-They're all in great condition this time.
Make sure you get full price.
Hurry. The ship is already here.
Tell me now.
What's the next game?
We don't know yet.
What do you mean?
You don't know?
We haven't been told yet.
Then go ask your boss.
I'm sure there's someone behind you!
If he knew, he would've told us already.
-I'm sure there's a reason.
-That's your problem.
I did everything you told me to.
Go tell him to find out now!
Go back and wait!
I'll tell you before the game begins.
That's bullshit!
What is it?
Pull.
-Calm down.
-If I don't find out what the game is,
they'll kill me in there tonight.
You won't find out anything like this.
Give us some time.
Do you think I'll trust scumbags like you?
What else can we do?
You go and find out.
And you.
You're staying here with me
until he gets back.
It'll be more dangerous
if we stay here like this.
We must return before morning roll call.
That's none of my fucking business!
I'm not going back
until I find out what the game is.
Fine, okay. Calm down.
Go up there and find out what the game is.
Okay.
Wait!
You have to take the key.
The key to go upstairs
is in my right pocket.
Don't try anything funny.
I'm not.
He needs it to enter the control room.
If you don't trust me,
you can throw it to him yourself.
Don't touch it.
-It's a bomb.
-A bomb?
This passage was made
for the VIPs to escape in an emergency.
Once they're out,
they set it off and bury the entire place.
What kind of people are the VIPs?
Not our business.
Number 29.
Emergency. The doc is escaping.
Shit.
Damn it.
Why do you want to know who the VIPs are?
I was just grateful
for our diving equipment and this passage.
They prepared it all for us.
Not only did you get more curious,
your voice seems to have changed.
Let me see your face.
Do you have to do this?
Should I kill you to find out?
Who are you?
Let me see your face.
Should I kill you to find out?
Don't come closer!
Calm down. We can still fix this.
How will you fix this?
By killing me?
Think about it.
Why would I kill you?
That'll only complicate things.
Things are already complicated.
Your friend is dead.
He wasn't a friend.
I'll throw those bodies
into the incinerator and burn them.
It won't leave a trace.
It's a huge problem
if a player goes missing,
but a missing soldier is
no problem at all.
Who am I?
What's important isn't who I am.
What's important is
the identity of the man you did this to.
The man you called a zombie.
The man with one kidney
who woke up on the table.
Do you know where his other kidney is?
In here.
It's in here.
He gave it to me.
-That man is my brother!
-No!
It was a woman.
A woman.
It wasn't a man.
I'll make sure
to find out what the next game is.
If you make a bigger scene and get caught,
both you and I will die in vain.
Trust me.
-We still have another chance.
-How can I trust a scumbag like you?
See?
I'm just another human like you.
Yes.
You just need to go back quietly.
If you return before bedtime is over,
you and I can both live.
Then what do I have to do?
Doctor.
Let's get you washed up first.
I'm telling the truth.
It was a woman.
How can I believe that?
Before we opened her up,
we took turns doing her.
Would we have done that to a guy?
If you still don't trust me,
go check the list.
-The list?
-There's a list of all the players
and their personal information.
-It even includes their medical records.
-Where?
Above the ladderway,
in the leader's room.
The leader?
You've seen him.
The one with a different mask.
I'll help you find your brother.
And you can have all the money I made
by selling the organs. I mean it!
Once we become a team…
Whether you sell
the dead bodies' organs or devour them,
I don't give a damn.
However,
you ruined the most important aspect
of this place.
Equality.
Everyone is equal
while they play this game.
Here, the players get to play a fair game
under the same conditions.
Those people suffered from inequality
and discrimination out in the world,
and we're giving them the last chance
to fight fair and win.
And you
broke that principle.
I'm sorry.
Sir,
we found another one.
It's Number 28.
There's one more,
the one who killed this one.
He could've escaped to the sea already.
The oxygen tanks are all here.
He's still here.
Find him.
LIST OF PLAYERS, 1999
LIST OF PLAYERS 1
Number 29 is gone too.
Find him.
He's not on the security cameras either.
He has to be in here.
All players, please line up in the middle.
Let me repeat.
-All players,
-Everyone, come out to the middle.
please line up in the middle.
Move it.
Damn it. What the hell
is the fuss about this time?
Boss, that doctor…
Get up.
Now!
He's very sick right now.
OCCUPATION: CHAFFEUR
LIST OF WINNERS
2015 28TH SQUID GAME
PLAYER 132, HWANG IN-HO
Hwang In-ho.
The year 2015…
LIST OF PLAYERS 1, 2015
Number 132…
Brother.
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon