What about the intruder?
We didn't find him yet.
Make sure you catch him.
The VIPs will arrive soon.
EPISODE 7
VIPS
Deok-su, you're finally back.
You…
How…
What?
Does it feel like
your dead mother's come back to life?
Those masked guys
said I was the weakest link.
Just like how we called someone who was
left without a partner when we were kids.
Hey, you've all heard of it too, right?
The weakest link!
Then they nicely escorted me back here.
Well,
they said that it's a beautiful rule
kids used to keep,
so the weakest kid doesn't turn
into an outcast.
God, damn.
Isn't that freaking cool?
Are you in here right now?
You made one mistake.
I always put the receiver down
the opposite way.
The bullet you shot
was for the Smith and Wesson M60 revolver,
the model that Korean police carry.
What's a cop doing here
alone without a partner?
I'm sure you have lots of questions.
Come out and talk with me.
I don't know how you got in,
but you can't leave this place
without my permission.
We found a body.
Where?
The northern coast of the island.
Don't make a big deal out of it.
He was just an old man
you got to know here.
That man's partner
was his wife.
We found this police ID.
HWANG JUN-HO
NATIONAL POLICE AGENCY
The VIPS have arrived.
Incinerate the body.
Let's end this. I can't do this anymore.
We can stop if the majority of us agree.
If nine of us agree,
we can get out of here.
Don't any of you want to leave?
If you wish to leave with me,
please stand up.
How do you call yourselves human?
Are you really going to continue
with this insanity?
Because of that money!
You all killed the one
you were closest to in this place
because of that money.
If we get out…
Will your wife come back to life
if we get out of here?
Will you be forgiven
for killing your wife?
If you're that tormented,
why did you come back alive?
You should've died instead of her.
That…
isn't just your wife
but the cost of everyone who died here.
-No.
-You want us to leave that and go?
You want us to leave
and start a shitty life
all over again from rock bottom
with this shitty guilt in our hearts?
Are you all ready to live like that?
If you can,
then go ahead and get up right now.
Get up and leave here!
No…
The VIPs have arrived.
Your shift is over.
Player 69, eliminated.
The fifth game will begin momentarily.
All players, follow staff's instructions
and proceed to the game hall
Welcome to the fifth game.
Before we begin the game,
please choose a mannequin before you
numbered from 1 through 16.
Let me repeat.
Before we begin,
please choose a mannequin before you
numbered from 1 through 16.
There are 16 people left,
and there are 16 numbers.
God created man on the sixth day
in this world.
I'm going back to that day God created
the sinless and innocent man.
Okay. Lucky number, seven.
What should I do?
The middle numbers are all taken.
Attention, please.
The numbers before you
are the order in which you'll be playing.
Please choose carefully.
Order?
The order we play?
Okay. If this is the order we play,
the front numbers are advantageous.
There's a high chance there's a time limit
like Red Light, Green Light and Honeycomb.
It's better to get a head start.
No.
Wait.
It'd be too dangerous to go first
without knowing the game.
From the back, I can watch those who play
first and make a plan like Tug-of-war.
Number 16?
I can't go with 16.
I don't want to go last.
No. 1? That means
I'll be starting the game off.
Then should I go last?
No, that doesn't seem right either.
Come on, Gi-hun!
Excuse me.
May I take No. 1?
I lived my entire life
hiding behind others like a coward.
I've never lived
like I was in control of my own life.
I keep saying I shouldn't,
but I always get scared.
Even today, I chickened out
and ended up choosing last again.
I want at least one chance
to be the owner of my life,
confidently at the very front.
Please.
Thank you!
Players, welcome to the fifth game.
The fifth game is Glass Stepping Stones.
Each stepping stone is made with
either of two types of glass,
tempered glass and normal glass.
Tempered glass is strong enough
to hold even two players' weight.
However, normal glass will break
even if just one player steps on it.
Players, you will guess
which one of the two tiles
is made of tempered glass,
and step only on those
among 18 pairs of tiles
to cross to the other side safely
and pass this game.
That means these numbers are…
The order in which you cross the bridge.
How do I tell which one is tempered glass?
You have 16 minutes.
You have 16 minutes to cross the bridge.
Then let the game begin.
Take your shoes off,
then go up on the bridge in order.
-What are you doing?
-We're losing time!
-Hurry up and go!
-Just jump!
-Are you just going to stand there?
-Hey.
If you don't go, I'll push you.
I'll go. I'll go, okay?
Please choose wisely, okay?
Good job!
That's good!
Yes, that's it.
Keep doing that one after the other.
-Good job.
-You can do it!
That's it. Great job.
He's gone.
First, it was left.
The second, right.
You can do it.
You got this.
Hurry up and go!
-There are 15 more tiles ahead of me.
-Hurry up!
-Jump!
-Stop stalling!
-We don't have time!
-The probability that I'll get to the end…
-You got this!
-two to the power of fifteen.
That's a 1-in-32,768 chance.
Shit.
Ma'am.
By any chance,
do you remember which way he went next?
I can't seem to remember.
It all happened too quickly.
Try to remember.
I need to get this right for you to live.
Well…
I think it was left.
No! He went right, then left.
No, he went left straight away.
No, it was right from there.
Are you sure…
he went left?
Yes.
So he went right.
There are ten tiles left,
and 11 people standing.
If they manage to choose
one or two right tiles,
we'll all be able to cross safely.
That might not be the case.
If people at the front
get scared and waste time,
it'll put us at the back in danger.
Our Father who art in heaven
-What the hell are you doing?
-Hallowed be thy name…
-Are you seriously praying right now?
-…thy will be done on earth
-What's he doing up there?
-as it is in heaven.
-Just go!
-Forgive us our trespasses…
-Cut that nonsense and get up.
-as we forgive those
-who trespass against us.
-It's your turn, idiot!
-And lead us not into temptation.
-Just go! Or we'll all die!
There is no order in which God calls us.
The day of judgment is upon us.
All of us…
will end up in Hell, anyway.
Do something to make him go.
If you don't,
I might have to push you forward.
If you don't want to die first,
make that praying jerk go forward.
-Get up already, you idiot!
-Let go.
Step forward, you crazy jerk!
Thank you, Lord.
Don't push me.
I'll go.
Don't worry. Why would I kill you?
You have to cross for me to live, right?
The left.
It's the left one.
Pull yourself together.
Okay.
Thanks.
Great job. Keep it up.
I think I know
which one the tempered glass is.
Really?
Can you really tell?
I got the hang of it.
The colors are different.
Dimwit. You don't know anything.
Hey, you assholes!
I'm not taking another step!
If you want to go, you can go first!
Damn it.
Bon appétit!
-What are you doing?
-Don't you understand Korean?
I'm not moving forward.
Quit your dirty tricks!
The rule is that we go in order.
Piss off, fucker.
This is hell. There are no rules in hell.
If you're dying to go, go first.
You fucker!
If you don't go, I'll push you.
Sure.
Sounds great, damn it.
Come at me! We'll all die here together!
Hey, assholes!
I'm not going to die for you to live.
So come at me!
Either you go first,
or we die here together.
It's one or the other.
Stop bluffing, bastard.
The time is ticking. You'll have to go.
Then wait around until we all die.
Damn it.
Damn it, you better go!
Hurry up and go!
Go yourself.
What freaking morons.
You acted like such a tough guy.
But you can't go?
Shit, how embarrassing.
Piss off, bitch.
I'm not going no matter what you say.
Deok-su.
I feel ashamed that I ever got it on
with a coward like you.
Then you can go first and die.
Move aside.
Really?
-You're going to go first?
-Yes.
It's me, Han Mi-nyeo.
I'm not going to stand around
with a coward like you
until I die.
You're welcome to do that.
Choose carefully.
What are you doing?
You naive idiot.
Did you really think
I'd die for you to live?
Let me go.
Remember?
We promised to stick together
to the very end.
You lunatic! Damn it!
Let go of me, bitch!
Damn it.
I told you I'd kill you
if you betrayed me.
Don't do this.
I'll go first, okay?
Please let go of me. Let go!
You coward.
Deok-su.
You know what?
Your dick is freaking small too.
Fuck.
Go check the VIP room.
What are you doing?
Stop stalling.
Wait, one second.
I know a way to tell these apart.
-How?
-I worked at a glass factory for 30 years.
Others can't see it,
but when you look at tempered glass
under light from an angle,
you'll be able to see faint stain marks.
Another hint is the sound.
Tempered glass is made
at high temperatures, above 700 degrees.
If you tap it with a hammer,
it rings clearer than normal glass.
Why are you telling us now?
If you had taken the lead--
Why should I?
Those people tried to kill me
every chance they had.
LONG-TERM WORK EXPERIENCE
IN GLASS MANUFACTURING
What's wrong?
What's the problem?
It's too dark to see.
The VIP has collapsed.
Is he alive?
He's fine.
What about the intruder?
We're searching for him.
Which one will it be? Make your decision!
I need to listen to the sound.
Do you have anything to throw?
Got anything?
Give me one more.
I need to hear the right one too.
I can't tell.
Then just go.
One of the diving equipment is gone.
He must have left
through the underwater cave.
Track it and get the boat ready.
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon