EPISODE 2
HELL
Sang-woo.
Thanks.
Thank you.
You two saved my life.
I'm glad you're alive.
All of you have made it through
the first game. Congratulations.
Let me announce
the results of the first game.
Out of 456 players,
255 players were eliminated,
and 201 players completed the first game.
Sir!
I'm so sorry.
I'll make sure I pay off my debts.
I'll pay them off at all costs.
Please, sir.
I have
a child.
I haven't even registered my baby's birth
because I haven't named my baby yet.
Please let me leave.
Sir, I'm so sorry.
Please. Please spare my life.
I'll find a way to pay off the debts.
-Please spare me.
-Me too.
I want to stop here. Please let me go.
Please spare my life.
Please let me go home.
Please spare me!
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
We are not trying to hurt you
or collect your debts.
Let me remind you
that we're here to give you a chance.
A chance?
You call this a chance?
You kill us
while making us play a kids' game.
How is this a chance?
We may be in debt,
but that doesn't mean we deserve to die.
This is just a game.
You killed all those people.
Yet you call this a game?
They were simply eliminated
for breaking the rules of the game.
If you just follow the rules,
you can leave this place safely
with the prize money we promised.
I don't need that stupid prize money.
Please just let me out.
Consent form clause 1:
A player is not allowed to stop playing.
Do you think you'll get away
with everything you're doing?
The police will barge in any minute now
to find us who've been missing.
He's right.
If you don't let us go,
they'll locate us by tracking our phones
and come find us!
-Then you'll be doomed!
-You're done for!
Consent form clause 2:
A player who refuses to play
will be eliminated.
Consent form clause 3:
Games may be terminated
if the majority agrees.
Is that correct?
That is correct.
Then, let us take a vote.
If the majority wish to leave this place,
then you must let us go.
As you wish, we will take a vote to decide
on the termination of the game.
Before we vote,
let me announce the prize money
accumulated from the first game.
A total of 255 players were eliminated
during the first game.
A hundred million won is at stake
for each player.
Therefore, 25.5 billion won of prize money
has been accumulated so far
into the piggy bank.
If you wish to give up now,
the 25.5 billion won will be sent
to the bereaved families
of the eliminated players,
100 million won each.
However, all of you will
return home empty-handed.
Excuse me.
If we make it through all six games,
how much do we get?
Since there were 456 players,
the total prize money is 45.6 billion won.
We will now start voting.
As you can see,
there are two buttons in front of you.
If you wish to continue playing,
press the green button with an O.
If you wish to stop playing,
press the red button with an X.
And after you finish voting,
move to the other side of the white line.
The voting will be done in reverse order
of the numbers on your chests.
Player 456, please cast your vote.
Player 453, please cast your vote.
Player 218.
Have you all gone insane?
Do you all want to continue this insanity?
So what if we leave?
Will it be any different if we leave?
Life out there is hell anyway, damn it.
She's right!
If we stop now,
we're only doing the dead ones a favor.
Only they'll get 100 million won.
We're the ones who won! That's not fair.
Please. Please don't do this.
We should go home.
I don't have a home to go back to.
In here, I stand a chance at least.
But out there?
I got nothing out there.
Let's stay and do this to the end!
I'd rather stay here and die trying
than die out there like a dog.
You jerk.
If you want to die, then go die alone.
Don't drag us into this, you little shit.
So quit yapping.
We will not condone any act
that impedes this democratic process.
Now, let us resume the voting process.
Now, this is the last voter.
Player 1.
My doctor said
there's a lump in my head.
Brain tumor.
If you wish to continue playing, press O.
If you wish to stop playing, press X.
The majority of the players
voted to terminate the game.
Therefore, this game is now terminated.
Those who want to leave can leave.
But let the ones who want to stay
continue playing.
Half of us died already!
We can't stop here!
He's right! Please let us continue!
Yes! Let us continue!
It's a pity that
we must say goodbye to you like this.
However, we will not seal off
the door of opportunity to you.
If the majority of you wish
to participate again,
we will restart the game.
Goodbye, then.
Help! There's a person here!
Is anybody there? Over here!
Will you shut up?
What?
Who are you?
Pickpocket? Is that you, pickpocket?
Unless you want to lie here all night,
try to untie me.
What?
Darn it. Where are we?
Hey. Can you untie me now?
Hey, I… Right.
You can get dressed first.
It's cold, isn't it?
I'm freezing too.
Man. Gosh. Yes, hurry up.
Man, my legs hurt. Hey.
Hey, you need to untie me now.
Come on. Hey.
Wait! What are you doing?
You need to untie me before you go.
Why should I?
Because I untied you!
Aren't you too old
to be that naive or stupid?
Once I untie you,
you'll hassle me
and demand your money back.
Well, that's that.
Okay, fine.
I'll forget about the money.
Just untie me, will you?
Do you mean that?
Yes, I really won't say anything
about the money.
How can I trust you?
I swear it on my mom.
Untie me now. It's freezing!
God damn it. That hurts.
Darn it.
Darn it. Come here.
My money… Give me my money back.
Give me… Darn it.
Give me my money back! Give it back! Man.
Damn it, give me my money.
I feel really bad for your mother.
You little… Hey, stop right there. Hey!
Hey! Stop right there!
Darn it!
Sir, where are we?
Yeouido.
Where exactly is Yeouido?
In the center of Seoul.
Sir, do you have your phone on you?
Can I use your phone?
Just one call.
That'll be 2,000 won.
CYBER POLICE: SUBPOENA HAS BEEN SENT.
SANG-WOO, CALL US NOW AND WE WON'T SUE.
MR. CHO SANG-WOO, YOUR LOANS ARE…
SEOUL POLICE: YOU ARE TO ATTEND AT ONCE.
Thank you.
Hi.
Yes, I had some work.
I'm sorry.
Thank you, sir.
Goodbye.
Wait.
-Do you have money for the bus?
-Sorry?
You said you live in Ansan.
You couldn't even pay for the ramyeon.
Do you have money for a ride?
-Money.
-I don't have any money.
I'll walk.
You're going to walk
all the way to Ansan from here?
Wait a bit, then take the bus.
I can't take that.
I don't have any money.
I can't pay you back.
I won't ask you to. Just take it.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
I'm not your sir,
so please stop calling me that.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Officer, I don't think you realize
the seriousness of this matter.
Okay, mister.
So you're saying some weird strangers
gathered hundreds of strangers in a field,
told them to play a game, then shot them?
Yes!
And not just one or two people.
They shot down over 200 people
without mercy.
And what was the game?
Red Light, Green Light.
Red Light, Green Light, the kids' game?
Yes.
They made grown-ups play that?
That's what I'm saying!
-And they shot everyone who got caught?
-Do I have to repeat myself?
Mister. So where is this place?
The place where they were killed.
They put me to sleep before they took me,
so I don't know.
What about the killers then?
They all had masks on.
Then how did you get out?
Well, the players took a vote.
The majority wanted to leave, so…
Wait, so the victims said
they wanted to leave,
then the murderers said,
"Be my guest, you may leave"?
Yes.
Why did you go there to begin with?
Well…
They said they'd give me money
for playing some games.
Money?
Yes, they said
they'd give us tens of billions of won.
All right, then.
Let me sum up everything you said.
Someone offered tens of billions of won
for playing games, so you followed.
They made you play Red Light, Green Light,
and they shot everyone who got caught.
But when you said you wanted to leave,
they let you go,
and you don't know what they look like
or where this all took place.
Am I correct?
Yes.
What's your name?
I'm Seong Gi-hun,
and I live in Ssangmun-dong.
Mr. Seong Gi-hun, do you have a guardian?
If you need any help,
we can contact a medical institution.
I'm a tax-paying citizen of Ssangmun-dong!
What do you take me for?
This is the business card they gave me.
You can just call them and find out!
Hello?
Hello, I'm sorry to call you so early.
May I ask you a question?
-Who is this?
-Well, I…
Right. I'm sorry to bother you,
but can I play some sort of game?
Game?
Yes, I'm pretty good at playing games.
You can ask me to play anything.
-I'll do my best--
-Hey.
Who the heck are you calling me this early
with this nonsense?
If you want to play games, go
to an internet cafe, you freaking pervert!
You dialed the wrong number!
-Officer, don't do this. Let go!
-Sorry, mister. Go home.
Are you sure you dialed the right number?
Are you really sure?
Just you wait.
I'll call and put you on the phone.
The number I dialed last time is
still here on my phone.
Darn it.
The number you have dialed does not exist.
Please call again
after checking the number.
Who was that? A drunk?
He's just insane.
Things are awfully hectic today.
Get a grip!
Will you keep coming back here?
I'll get going. Have a good day.
Keep up the good work.
Mom.
I'm home.
What the…
Mom!
Where is she?
The phone is turned off.
You will be forwarded to voicemail…
Where did this old lady go?
She even left the door open.
Sang-woo.
What are you doing here?
Is it because of your debt?
Hey, you're the pride of Ssangmun-dong,
the genius born and raised here,
who got accepted to SNU Business School
as valedictorian. Don't worry.
You can always earn money.
Go tell your mom all about it
and make a fresh start.
How will I earn
six billion won?
Six billion?
Wait, I thought it was 600 million.
There are things they don't know.
Did you invest in stocks
while working at a securities firm?
Stocks weren't much.
I also dealt in futures.
Futures?
You bet that much on your future?
What kind of bet was it
that you used that much money?
-Did you get a girlfriend?
-It's not that kind of "future."
Never mind.
My gosh.
Can't you just file
for personal bankruptcy or whatever?
I heard you won't have to pay off
your debts if you do that.
I used all of my mom's properties
as collateral as well as mine.
Including her house
and her shop, everything.
Hello?
Yes, this is he.
What?
24-HOUR EMERGENCY MEDICAL CENTER
She's diabetic.
Left untreated,
it developed complications.
She must've been in a lot of pain.
Did you have no idea?
She can be treated, right?
In the worst-case scenario,
she might need to have her feet amputated.
Let's have her hospitalized and watch
how things go as she gets treated.
Mom!
Mom, where are you going?
He said you need to be hospitalized.
I'm fine.
No, you are not fine.
You can't even walk properly.
Forget it.
You haven't come home for days
doing whatever you do.
Now you suddenly show up
and try to play the good son?
Mom, don't be so foolish.
It will get worse if you don't treat it!
What if I do? If I'm hospitalized,
who's going to pay our rent?
Also, do you have any idea
how much it costs to stay in the hospital,
let alone the treatment?
You have your insurance!
What did you say? Insurance?
Don't you remember?
You canceled everything
and used up all the money.
Will you please get a grip?
Goodness.
Gi-hun.
I'm too tired.
I'm too tired to go on.
Let's stop this here.
Darn it. I'll bring money!
I'll bring money home, okay?
Yes, Mom.
I'm on my way to his room.
I'm sure he's fine.
You know how he dodges calls
from time to time.
I'll call everyone
who might know where he is.
If I still can't reach him,
I'll report him missing tomorrow.
I'm a police officer, remember?
I'll find him.
Yes, Mom. Don't worry too much.
CYBER DORMITORY
How long has it been
since he last came in?
Well, I don't check on everyone here
every day.
But he was supposed to pay his rent
a week ago.
I've stopped by every day since then,
but he hasn't come in
or picked up his phone.
Well…
By the way, about his rent…
Otherwise, you'll have to
move his stuff out right away.
I'll take a look,
then give you his rent later.
Take your time, then.
THEORY OF DESIRE, JACQUES LACAN
A drunk?
He's just insane.
Things are awfully hectic today.
Kids, come and have some ice cream.
Yes! Ice cream!
What's wrong?
I thought you wanted ice cream.
What happened to your face?
Did you fight with your friends?
If you keep silent like that,
I'm going to leave.
I don't want to stay here.
You said you'd bring Mom soon.
You said we'd all live together
if I just waited a month.
Cheol.
-It's…
-All the kids say you lied.
They said I'd never leave this place.
They said you abandoned me here.
No.
Mom and Dad are going to come.
I'll make sure they do.
We'll all get to live
under the same roof next year.
You know me, right?
You know I always keep my promises.
Yes, that guy. Red Light, Green Light.
Why do you need that lunatic's name,
Detective Hwang?
Well, I caught a glimpse of him yesterday,
and I think he might be
an old acquaintance.
Really?
What was his name?
Seong something
who lives in Ssangmun-dong.
Seong Gi-hun.
Seong Gi-hun of Ssangmun-dong.
You're right. Seong Gi-hun.
Do you know him?
Yes, I think so.
Could you get me his address?
Hey, Ali! Long time no see!
Hey, Ali.
-Why are you dodging my calls?
-You called?
I had no idea.
Why? Is something wrong?
Sir, pay me all the wages you owe me.
Hey, how many times do I have to tell you?
I don't have any money right now.
Our business isn't doing well, so--
I couldn't have my finger treated.
I couldn't afford the hospital fee.
I'm going back home now.
Please, give me my money.
Damn it.
Go ask the other guys if they got paid.
I can only pay you once I get paid!
Hey, I'm in lots of pain all over my body.
But I can't go see a doctor
because I have no money.
You said you'd pay me.
Please pay me. It has been six months.
Damn it, what's with you?
Hey, we'll talk later.
I'm a little busy right now.
Sir, give me my money.
Sir, please give me my money.
How dare you touch me, you little shit?
Don't swear at me!
You freaking idiot!
You got money here!
-You son of a bitch!
-My money!
Let me go, you idiot.
Give me my money!
Hey, you can't just leave!
SOUTHERN MEN, NORTHERN WOMEN
I understand very well
what your situation is like.
But you know,
it's impossible to find brokers
once they've fled with the money.
You aren't the only victim.
Some of the victims went all the way
to Dandong to catch them,
but they were caught by the Chinese police
and almost dragged back to the North.
Then, Is there any other way?
You'll need to hire another broker.
But as you probably know,
you'll have to start all over again…
How much?
First off, they'll have to begin
by locating your parents again.
And the border security
has been tightened,
so the price for helping them
cross the river shot up.
So how much?
At the least…
you'll need 40 million won.
Forty million.
That's just the price
for taking them to China.
If you want to bring them to the South--
It's hot!
That's freaking hot! Damn it!
I trusted what you said last time
and sent the money.
The money I risked my life to get.
Hey,
I really had no idea, okay?
I didn't know
they'd run off with your money.
I swear.
I will
bring the money.
But if you deceive me again,
I'll cut your throat open next time.
Get it?
Okay.
It's so hot.
SANG-WOO'S FISH STORE
Have you been eating all right?
Yes, I've been eating well,
so don't worry.
I doubt American food is to your taste.
What have you been eating?
It's okay, Mom.
There are lots of Korean restaurants here.
Really? That's a relief.
When are you coming back?
It's taking longer than expected,
so I'm not sure.
-It might take a while.
-I see.
It must be really tough for you.
Mom.
Yes? What is it?
Excuse me.
I'll take three squids to parboil.
Okay, one second.
Sang-woo, I have a customer.
Don't get me anything when you come back.
I don't need anything, okay?
Okay.
All right.
Don't skip meals and dress warmly.
Talk to you again. I love you, son.
Did you say squid?
Goodness, he always gets me
a little something
whenever he goes abroad
on a business trip.
You must have a wonderful son.
He graduated from Seoul University.
Business Administration.
Goodness, Business Administration at SNU?
Not only is he smart,
but he's also handsome.
Is he married?
Not yet.
How old is he?
Shall I set him up with someone?
But my son has high standards.
Excuse me.
Are you Mr. Cho Sang-woo's mother?
Yes, Cho Sang-woo is my son.
Where is he right now?
He's in the US on a business trip.
-Why are you looking for him?
-We're the police.
An arrest warrant has been issued
for Mr. Cho Sang-woo
citing acts of embezzlement, forgery
of private documents,
and other financial crimes.
What?
Arrest who?
Goodness, detectives.
There must be a misunderstanding.
My son would never do anything illegal.
If you reach your son,
tell him to make a voluntary appearance.
If he keeps fleeing like this,
it'll affect him negatively
when he's put on trial.
Who is it?
TIME: MIDNIGHT, JUNE 23
PLACE: SAME AS PREVIOUS
Where did you get this money?
Ali, where did you get this money?
Listen carefully.
Buy tickets for the earliest flight
for you and our kid, and go home first.
What about you?
You two should go first.
I'll be there
as soon as my job here is done.
Something is going on with you, right?
Don't ask anything for now.
You need to pack up and leave right away.
I hope you can understand my problem.
I love you. You and our child.
I got no money.
HEALING PUB
Just lend me three million.
I'll pay you back in two months.
You shouldn't talk money between friends.
And you know my situation.
Of course, I do.
I wouldn't be asking you
if it weren't so bad.
If I have to,
I'll work here as a deliveryman.
What do you mean, a deliveryman?
Look at my pub.
I can't even afford the rent.
Then I'll pay you back in a month.
I can if I work two jobs
as a chauffeur and a deliveryman.
Come on.
The doctor said she needs
to have surgery right away, but--
Honey.
Shouldn't you get back inside?
I will soon.
Get inside right now!
And put out your cigarette!
Hello.
-Gi-hun.
-Yes?
You shouldn't smoke
in front of someone else's store.
Right.
You…
Sir.
It's you, right?
Player 456.
Yes, sir.
That's me.
What are you doing in this neighborhood?
I live around here.
I see.
Do you live in this neighborhood too?
No.
I have a friend who lives nearby.
I have no place to go at the moment,
so I'm staying there for a while.
Gosh.
Would you like to sit?
Sure.
I can't believe I ran into you here.
What are the chances?
I guess
we were meant to meet.
Gosh.
Well, would you like some?
Sure.
Right.
Is your head okay?
Are you allowed to drink?
It's all right.
Gosh.
I'm sorry I don't have any food.
It's okay.
RAMYEON
Wait.
Sir, is this really okay?
Aren't you having a bit much?
I'm fine.
I…
decided to go back there.
Go back where?
There?
You know,
I don't have long left to live anyway.
I don't want to
sit around waiting for my death like this.
You never know.
I might end up winning in there.
When we played Red Light, Green Light,
I finished the game before you did.
But still, that place is…
After I came back out here,
I realized everything they said was true.
Life out here is more tormenting.
Boss!
Why are you so late?
These drunks got into a fight
at my bar right when I was about to leave.
You know what it's like.
All kinds of losers come out
on Friday nights to party.
Where's the money?
That's all I could get on short notice.
I can collect more for you
after the weekend.
Anyway, I heard our Big Boss
sent out all the boys he could
to Incheon and Ilsan to look for you.
Where have you been hiding?
I can't discuss that here.
Did you drive here?
Yes, this way.
So this is the invitation to
that "Red Light, Green Light" thing?
That's right.
They sent it to me yesterday.
It looks like they're about to go again.
So gather as many boys as you can
by Tuesday.
And get a few guns too.
-Guns?
-They carry guns.
But only one guy comes to pick us up.
We'll beat up that masked guy
and break into their safe.
I mean, even if
everything you said is true--
You little shit.
What do you mean, even if? It is true.
I'm sorry, sir.
Those guys keep tens of billions of won
in a huge piggy bank.
If we manage to get them good,
we won't have to deal with drunks
at bars to make a living anymore.
But, Boss…
all of the boys assume you went into
hiding after pissing off the Big Boss.
Everyone in Incheon thinks so.
I don't think I can convince anyone.
Look, you jerk. I'm saying I'll rob them
and pay him all back.
Boss.
So how much did you lose
at the casino in the Philippines?
How did you know that?
Boss, you should've known when to stop.
Have you gone nuts, you bastard?
Hey, Deok-su.
"Deok-su"?
Idiot.
Those casino operators
from the Philippines came here
to take your liver, kidney, and eyes
instead of the money you owe.
You're doomed, you dumbass.
Come at me, you bastards.
Money?
Yes.
How much?
About…
two million won.
Two million won?
Yes.
Don't you think you're too brazen?
You've never even paid me any alimony
or child support.
How could you come
and beg me for money again?
I'm sorry.
It's for my mom's hospital bills.
How sick is she?
She has severe diabetes.
She needs surgery.
I don't have any money.
We can barely make ends meet.
Please.
My mom was really good to you.
Imagine how desperate I am
to be asking you.
I'll make sure I pay you back.
I really have no money.
My husband gives me living expenses.
Then could you ask him--
Are you nuts?
Hey.
What should I tell him it's for?
Go. Leave now.
-Hey.
-The kids' dad will be home soon.
Why do you keep calling him the kids' dad?
I'm Ga-yeong's dad!
What? Dad?
What did you ever do for her?
You think you deserve to be her dad?
You weren't even there when she was born!
That was…
You know the story already! I couldn't go!
My coworker collapsed--
I collapsed too!
I practically crawled to the hospital!
Had I been a little late,
I would've lost her!
My coworker died that day,
right before my eyes!
He couldn't even go to the hospital!
Honey, we're home.
You came back early.
Dad.
Mom!
He was in the neighborhood
and stopped by to see Ga-yeong.
Now that I saw her, I'll get going.
-Are you leaving?
-Yes, I have an important meeting.
Ga-yeong, goodbye, now.
-I'll come to see you again.
-Okay.
Like this…
Why did he come this time?
-Why did you let him in the house?
-Sorry.
I came back from getting groceries,
and he was waiting at the front door.
Wait.
What is this?
I heard you needed money.
Thank you.
I'll pay you back.
You don't have to.
Instead,
I need you to stop seeing my family.
Ga-yeong is having a tough time.
We'll move to the US soon,
but if you keep showing up like this--
You bastard!
Do you think money solves everything?
Dad.
Mr. Seong Gi-hun?
Yes?
Hwang Jun-ho, Dobong Police.
You recently made a report
at the substation.
That they abducted people
to make them play games.
And that…
people were killed there.
That? I just made it up.
I was drunk and bored,
so I made up that story.
My brother had the same card
as the one you had.
And he's currently missing.
I just picked it up on the street
and kept it in my pocket.
Mr. Seong.
Please help me.
I need to find my brother.
I'm sorry.
I'm not in a position
to help anyone at the moment.
HALLYM UNIVERSITY
HANGANG SACRED HEART HOSPITAL
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon