EPISODE 8
FRONT MAN
Why did you do it?
What is it you want to say?
Why did you push him?
You got lucky
and chose the very last place.
I guess it made you very lax.
What if that man ended up
holding out like that thug?
What would you have done?
It was the last tile.
He was clearly going to move.
How can you be so sure?
He knew how to tell apart
the tempered glass,
but just watched people fall down and die.
In the end, both you and I
crossed that bridge alive thanks to him.
That's bullshit. I don't know about you,
but I'm not alive because of him.
I'm alive right now
because I tried damn hard to stay alive.
No matter what excuse you say,
you still killed an innocent man.
Get a grip!
We have to kill everyone else anyway
to leave with that money.
Shouldn't you be grateful
that I did the dirty work for you?
Would you have pushed if it were me?
Damn it.
Gi-hun!
Do you know why your life is so pathetic?
Because you ask such dumb questions
even in this kind of situation.
Because you're such a nosy-ass idiot
who's freaking slow,
and always have to get into trouble
to know it's trouble.
Sure.
It's all my fault I ended up like this.
I'm slow and incompetent.
I'm a nosy dimwit
who lives off the back of his old mother.
But
why is the pride of Ssangmun-dong,
the genius Cho Sang-woo of SNU, here?
Rolling around this shithole
with a dimwit like me.
Is that also my fault?
We sincerely congratulate and commend you
for successfully making it
through five games.
You've now become the finalists,
and we've prepared a special gift for you.
Before we reveal the gift,
please change into the outfit we prepared.
Bring him alive.
JUNE 29, MONDAY
CHIEF
-Jun-ho!
-Chief.
-Where the hell are you?
-Chief, can you hear me?
-I haven't seen or heard from you in days!
-I'll explain everything later.
-Who the hell do you think you are?
-I'm on an island
-somewhere in the southwestern sea.
-What?
Can you locate this phone
and send backup right away?
What? Backup?
I need backup. I need the coast guard
and a police squad at least.
What? I can't hear you!
I'll send you the photos and videos.
-You can check those.
-Hey.
-I'll call you again.
-Slow it down. What--
Tonight's feast is prepared
as a token of gratitude for the sacrifice
and effort that you finalists have made,
and to encourage you to perform
more splendidly in the last game.
Please do not worry and enjoy your feast.
RE-SEND
He's over there.
Police! Drop your weapons and surrender!
I already alerted the police
about everything you did.
The coast guard will arrive shortly.
I don't know.
Have the Korean police
ever been so enthusiastic?
Besides, you barely get
a phone signal in this area.
I don't know what you sent,
but I doubt it was sent.
If you turn yourself in now,
you can make a mitigation plea.
If you drop your gun
and hand the phone over now,
I might let you live.
Stop right there!
That gun holds five bullets.
But, according to police regulation,
one chamber must remain empty
and one must be filled with a blank shell.
That's three live rounds.
You already shot once to kill a guy
and another one to break the lock.
That means there is only one bullet
left in your gun.
One bullet is enough to kill you.
Give up.
I warned you. If you take another step…
It's over.
Come with me.
Do as I say.
And you will live.
Who
are you?
In-ho.
Let's go.
Come with me.
In-ho…
In-ho, why…
Sae-byeok.
Don't worry.
I'm not here to kill you.
You've been dozing.
I would've killed you already if I wanted.
I only brought this because of him.
For protection.
You don't look too well.
No. I'm fine.
Then why did you have
so much food leftover?
It just wasn't good.
Stop lying.
If I'm hurt?
Will you treat me?
Don't mind me
and worry about yourself.
Hey, Sae-byeok.
Let's stick together
for the next game.
No matter what it is,
we'll help each other like a team.
Then we can win against him.
We'll each take half and leave this place.
What will you do
once you get out of here with that money?
I'll pay off my debt first.
Then open up a business for my mom
at the marketplace.
It's her wish to run a proper business
at a store rather than a stall.
And…
I want to be a proper dad…
to my daughter for once.
How old is she?
Ten.
She's the same age as my brother.
Where's your brother right now?
At a children's home.
I promised to bring him back
once I made money.
And bring my mom too.
I promised to do that once I made
enough money to buy a house for us.
Half of that prize will be
more than enough for that.
Mister.
Let's make a promise.
What promise?
That if either one of us…
makes it out of here alive,
we'll look after each other's family.
Don't say that.
We'll beat him and get out together.
Promise me, still.
Promise me you'll look after my brother.
Shush.
Don't do it.
You aren't that kind of person.
Hey.
Hey, what's wrong?
Hey, you're…
You're…
When did this happen?
When did you get hurt?
Damn it.
Mister.
Yes?
I want to go home.
Hey, Sae-byeok. Stay with me.
Don't let yourself go. Stay right here.
I'll go get a doctor.
Excuse me! Help!
She's lost a lot of blood!
Please help!
A person is dying in here!
Is anybody out there?
Hey, assholes!
A person is dying here!
You need to keep her alive
if you want her to play the damn game!
Please, answer me!
Hey,
could you please get a doctor?
She lost a lot of blood. Hurry! Please.
She's…
Sae-byeok.
Hey.
No. No, Sae-byeok.
No, Sae-byeok.
In-ho, why…
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon