Thanks.
-Gi-hun.
-Yes?
Never mind.
Thank you.
Sorry?
I lived because I copied your method.
Sirs!
You're alive.
I was worried.
Did you think I would die that easily?
I'm Seong Gi-hun of Ssangmun-dong.
Old sir, are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
It's all thanks to him.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said we should split up.
Don't say that.
It's not like you knew.
Besides, I chose the umbrella.
It's okay.
I'm glad everyone is fine.
We will now announce
the results of the second game.
Out of 187 players, 79 were eliminated.
The prize money accumulated this round
is 7.9 billion won.
The prize money accumulated so far
is 34.8 billion won.
EPISODE 4
STICK TO THE TEAM
Your mealtime begins now.
All players,
please form a line in the center.
This is all?
Those jerks.
Just a piece of bread before the game.
And this is all they give us
after our near-death experience?
Are they kidding me?
All right. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Hey, what are you doing?
Let's enjoy the food together.
Give me an egg and a soda.
We didn't get anything either.
One, two, three, four, five.
You're missing food for five people!
We prepared food
for the exact number of players.
Then why don't you have any left?
Give me my food!
We prepared food
for the exact number of players.
Excuse me.
Those people…
They took the food twice. I saw them.
Damn it, this is freaking annoying.
Have you never seen a person eat before?
Who do you think you are?
Why did you steal others' food?
Right, is this yours?
What's your name?
Is your name written on this?
I don't see it.
Give it back. It's mine.
Give it back to me!
You asshole.
It broke because of you, asshole!
How come a scrawny guy like you
is so greedy for food? You bastard!
Hey, I'm trying to say
that we need to share.
Is that so hard, you jerk?
You bastard!
Excuse me. Hey, wake…
He's dead.
Excuse me!
Do you hear me?
A person has died.
He just died.
That bastard just killed him.
He just killed a person!
Can't you hear me?
A man just died!
This isn't right!
We shouldn't be
killing each other like this!
Player 271, eliminated.
You there.
Why aren't you doing your job?
I'm sorry.
How may I help you?
Did you forget the rules?
You do not speak
before your superior allows you.
Lights-out in 30 minutes.
-Hurry. It'll be bedtime soon.
-Please return to the quarters now.
We can't fall asleep tonight.
Anything can happen after lights-out.
Those guys are definitely up to no good.
If anyone gets attacked,
we have to stick together and fight.
Come over to our side if anything happens.
All right.
Sir.
Sir?
You can't go to sleep
even after the lights go out, okay?
Why not?
Things will be a little dangerous tonight.
Keep your eyes open.
We'll come here if anything happens.
Okay. All right.
Hey, pickpocket.
Will you be all right?
It looked like you and that thug
weren't on good terms.
So what?
If anything happens after lights-out,
we're all meeting by my bed.
You should join us.
I don't trust people.
Especially people
who ended up in a place like this.
Are you seriously saying that to me?
You don't trust people
because they're trustworthy.
It's because
you have nothing else to lean on.
Where's the delivery team?
Number 28, why are you here alone?
Number 29 didn't show up.
-Was there an accident?
-I don't know.
Then you'll need to deliver this alone.
I can't go underwater by myself.
It's too dangerous.
Stop chatting and tell me now.
What's tomorrow's game?
Are you sure?
If I get eliminated,
you can't do this anymore.
Worry about that
after you survive the night.
What do you mean?
A fight will break out.
They gave them less food on purpose
to provoke a fight.
They're weeding out the weaklings
before the next game begins.
It's all part of the game.
We can't protect you when you're in there.
Go back and find a way to live.
A way to live?
Stick with the strongest team.
That's the only way.
Let me join…
your side.
Why should we?
What are you good at?
I'm a doctor outside.
I'll be of use.
So what?
Will you give us shots
if we catch a cold in here?
Once the lights are out,
sit quietly in a corner.
Don't even breathe.
If I hear you breathe,
I'll come for you.
I know
what the next game is.
Two minutes until lights-out.
The special game will begin momentarily.
Management, soldiers, and workers,
please move to your designated locations.
Let me repeat.
Management, soldiers, and workers,
please move to your designated locations.
Thirty seconds until lights-out.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one.
So you saw me?
Bitch.
Begin.
You asshole!
Gi-hun. Are you okay?
-Sir.
-Yes. Thanks.
Where's the old man?
Where is he? Where's the old man?
-He's not here.
-Sir…
Sir? Sir!
Sir!
Die!
Help!
You're here.
You told me to.
Hey, Ssangmun-dong.
Why are you butting in?
It's good for you too with fewer people.
She's on our side too.
Damn it.
Please,
stop!
I'm…
scared.
At this rate, we'll all die!
Everyone is going to die!
I'm so scared.
Stop it!
-End the game.
-If you keep going like this,
everyone will die!
Drop your weapon.
Turn around.
Player 277, eliminated.
Player 74, eliminated.
Player 198, eliminated.
Player 87, eliminated.
-Player 456.
-Player 222, eliminated.
-Is there a man named Hwang In-ho here?
-Player 301, eliminated.
-Player 416, eliminated.
-We do not know each other's names.
Player 361, eliminated.
Player 328, eliminated.
Player 103, eliminated.
Player 198, eliminated.
Player 6, eliminated.
Player 206, eliminated.
Player 233, eliminated.
Player 239, eliminated.
Are you all right?
What?
When did you climb all the way up there?
It was dangerous.
We were worried
because we couldn't find you.
It's a relief none of us were badly hurt.
Why don't we take this opportunity
to exchange names?
Come to think of it,
we don't even know each other's names.
I know your name.
Ssangmun-dong.
Ssangmun-dong is the town I live in.
My name is Seong Gi-hun.
Seong Gi-hun of Ssangmun-dong.
What's your name?
Ali.
Ali Abdul.
Which country are you from?
Pakistan.
Pakistan?
Where is that?
Right above India.
That's right.
Of course.
This guy here graduated
from Seoul University, Business--
I'm Cho Sang-woo.
Do I have to say?
We're on the same side now.
We at least need to know each others'
names to build a bit of trust.
Kang Sae-byeok.
Sae-byeok?
That's a nice name.
Doesn't really suit you, though.
Old sir, what's your name?
What?
My name?
My…
My name is…
Well, it's…
My…
name is…
Sir, you must've been
very frightened earlier.
When I'm really stressed out,
I tend to forget my home address
and resident registration number too.
It'll be okay once you get some rest.
Damn it.
Are you really a doctor?
What if I'm not?
You weren't stabbed too deep,
so you should be fine.
Once we get out of here,
I'll treat it again at my hospital.
What a pretentious dickhead.
Your business obviously went under,
seeing as you're here.
I'm going to leave this place…
with that.
Those bastards.
They set everything up for us
to kill them. Why'd they stop us?
We could've ended this
without playing any games.
If we kill everyone who's left,
won't we just
get to take all that?
We'll get another chance
if we survive the next game.
Isn't that so, Doc?
It's done.
This is why people say
you need a doctor in your family.
We got rid of quite a few.
It went from 107 to 80, so did we kill 27?
Right, babe?
"Babe"?
Is that right?
I don't know about that.
Mister,
how old do I look?
Forty-nine.
I shouldn't have helped you
during the Honeycomb game.
Maybe 39?
Last chance.
Nineteen?
You're very witty, babe.
Then, shouldn't I
be rewarded?
I'll think about it in the restroom.
I need to take a leak.
Babe.
You and that quack are hiding something.
There's nothing to hide.
Babe.
Will you…
really stick with me to the end?
Don't you deceive me.
Okay. Trust me.
You and I will get out of here.
What's your name, babe?
Why do you ask?
I want to know.
Deok-su.
Jang Deok-su.
If you betray me,
I'll kill you.
I might die right now
because of you.
Everyone, it's now time to go to sleep.
Good work today.
SHAPES, RANK, MASKED LEADER, GUN MASSACRE,
RIOT, ABETTING MURDER, MY BROTHER
Morse code?
Number 29.
Sir.
-Yes?
-Did you stay up all night?
I was afraid they might attack again.
You must be so tired.
I'm fine.
You don't get much sleep once you get old.
I wasn't much help,
so the least I can do is
stand night watch.
The third game will begin momentarily.
Follow the staff's instructions
and proceed to the game hall.
Let me repeat.
The third game will begin momentarily.
Starting head count.
Please wait in front of your door.
Head count complete.
Welcome to your third game.
This game will be played as a team.
All players,
please divide into teams of ten people.
You have ten minutes, ten minutes.
Let me repeat.
This game will be played as a team.
All players,
please divide into teams of ten people.
You have ten minutes, ten minutes.
Get guys who look strong.
Okay.
What about her?
If the game is played by teams of ten,
maybe it's Tail Tag
or Why Did You Come to My House.
If it's Tail Tag, we need to be fast.
If it's Why Did You Come to My House,
it's just Rock-Paper-Scissors.
What should we do?
We already have an elderly man
and a woman,
so we need to find more men.
What if they make us play
Elastics or Gonggi?
Women are better at those.
That's true, but probability-wise,
men are better at most games.
We're betting our lives right now.
Which side will it be?
We just need five more people.
Let's split up and bring one each.
Hide your hand.
It'll make you look weak.
Boss, this guy wants to join us.
Hey, go over there and find more guys.
Sir. Have you found a team yet?
-No.
-Then you should join us. We have a team.
The thing is,
I have to stick with my wife.
Is that all right?
I'm sorry.
We already have many women on our team.
Excuse me. If you're looking
for a team, let's join up.
Excuse me.
If you don't have a team yet,
do you want to join us?
Let's team up next time.
Babe.
No way. You're joking with me, right?
My team is already full. Can't you see?
We have exactly ten people.
Babe, don't be like that.
I'm sorry.
I'll be better.
Babe, I'll do anything.
I'm good at everything.
You know that, babe.
So…
let's split up just for this game
then meet again for the next one,
all right?
Babe.
Why should we split up?
You said we'd stick together to the end.
Babe.
Can you really do without me?
I can't do this without you, Babe.
Get off!
God damn it. You're so damn clingy.
Stop calling me babe.
If you call me that again,
I'll rip that mouth off.
Asshole.
Are you finally showing your true colors?
Jang Deok-su.
You scumbag.
I told you that I'll kill you
if you betray me.
I'm so scared.
Ms. Han Mi-nyeo.
Good luck with your game today, okay?
She's not worth the effort.
What?
Join me.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine?
Wait, is there someone
who couldn't bring anyone?
I'm sorry.
Who brought you here?
This one.
I told you that we're only getting men.
Things seem pretty grim here.
Did I join the wrong team?
Then I'll see myself out.
Wait.
Just sit there.
We don't even know
what we're going to play next.
We don't have much time either.
Let's find one more person
and make it ten first.
Who would volunteer
to join this weak team?
Once everyone finds a team,
we'll end up with someone left out.
I didn't get left out.
Boys, I'll give you
a special chance to join me.
You boys are very lucky today. My gosh.
I'd be much more useful
than these scrawny girls.
On top of that, I'm good at everything
except for the things I'm not.
The time for deciding teams is over.
All teams, form a line
at the entrance of the game hall.
Wait.
We aren't playing here?
Welcome to the third game.
You're going to play Tug-of-War.
You will pull a rope on that tower
to drop your opponents down below to win.
Now, I will draw lots
to decide which teams will play first.
Everyone, please sit down.
I will draw the lot
for the team on the left tower.
Team One. Please stand up.
Next, I will draw the lot
for the team on the right tower.
Team Seven. Please stand up.
Team One and Seven will play first.
Team One and Seven,
please enter the towers.
Kill them!
Die!
Eliminated players are No. 245,
No. 120, No. 37, No. 408,
No. 27, No. 273, No. 58,
No. 243, No. 327, and No. 241.
I will draw lots for the next round.
Team Four.
Team Five.
Shit.
It's a sausage fest.
Team Four and Team Five,
please enter the towers.
What a shame.
I wanted to kill you guys myself.
Don't be so dispirited.
Tug-of-War isn't really about strength.
Then what? Can we win by talking?
In Tug-of-War, with a good strategy
and good teamwork,
you can win even if your team is weaker.
The only one who can save us now
is the Lord.
You're barely standing, old man.
Stop talking nonsense
and save your strength.
Let's hear him out at least.
I played my share of Tug-of-War
in my hometown when I was young,
and I rarely ever lost.
Even when there was a ssireum athlete
on the other team,
putting the odds very much against us.
Listen closely,
and I'll tell you how I beat them
back in the day.
First off, the leader is very important.
That person is closest
to the leader of the opposition,
and the rest of the team
looks at the back of their leader.
If the leader seems weak or dispirited,
then the game is already over.
Then at the end of the rope,
you'll need someone dependable
like the anchor of a ship,
Placing people is also important.
Place the rope in the middle,
and people go on alternating sides.
Place your two feet straight forward,
and stick the rope between your armpits.
That way, you can put in
all of your strength.
And lastly,
this is the most important thing.
When the game starts,
for the first ten seconds
you just have to hold out.
You should practically lie down.
Push your lower abdomen up to the sky,
and push your head back to the point
you can see the groin
of the person behind you.
If you do that, the other team
won't be able to pull us to their side.
Hold out for just ten seconds like that.
Then the opposition will get flustered
thinking, "Why won't they even budge?"
Because they would have believed
that they were much stronger.
If you can hold out for that long,
there will be a moment
when the opponents' rhythm breaks.
Pull!
Pull yourselves together!
Do something! God damn it!
Pull yourselves together and listen up!
When I give the sign,
just take three steps forward!
Go forward? Are you crazy?
We have to make them trip!
That's bullshit!
Let's give it a shot!
No, I can't do it!
If you can't, you'll die!
On the count of three! One!
Two!
Three!
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon