CHIEF, I CAN'T GO TO THE STATION TODAY.
I'LL CONTACT YOU LATER
EPISODE 3
THE MAN WITH THE UMBRELLA
Begin.
Player inspection.
WORK EXPERIENCE: DRAGON MOTORS 16 YEARS,
GAYEONG CHICKEN 2 YEARS, CHAFFEUR 5 YEARS
WORK EXPERIENCE: HAEIL MOVERS 5 YEARS,
LOUSY MOVERS 7 YEARS, BANGA LABOR 5 YEARS
HWANG JUN-HO
NATIONAL POLICE AGENCY
You there!
It's just…
I felt seasick.
Did you forget the rule?
You do not speak
before your superior allows you.
Go standby in the cabin.
Sir.
Sir!
Are you all right?
It's you.
Player 456.
Yes.
I thought you were gone for good.
I'm not going to die that easily.
Of course, you won't.
I got to leave thanks to you,
then I came back thanks to you.
You can't die first.
A lot of people came back.
You're right.
I guess everyone had a tough time.
Gosh.
There's the woman who couldn't
even name her kid. She came back too.
You're right.
I wonder if she named her kid
before she came back.
Goodness.
Gi-hun.
Hey, Sang-woo.
You're here.
I didn't think you'd come.
Me neither.
What about you?
Did you see your mom?
Good sirs!
It's my savior!
I'm glad to see you again, sir.
Thank you very much
for giving me the bus fare.
You gave him the bus fare?
He said he'd walk from Yeouido to Ansan.
That's heart-warming.
It's like we're comrades from boot camp.
What's a boot camp?
You know, in the army,
where you shoot guns and train.
I know!
A place where soldiers live together?
That's right.
Wait.
Now that we're on the subject,
why don't we do this as a team
like we're in the army?
You're right. We have no idea
what we're going to play.
It's better to form a group
to be prepared for anything.
Listen. Why don't you join us?
He's amazingly strong.
You saw it, right?
He lifted me up with one hand.
Can I really join you two?
Yes, sure.
You can be the private, a new recruit.
He's a competent corporal,
and I'm a sergeant soon to go home.
Thank you, sir.
-And drop the "Sir."
-Hey.
If it's all right with you,
can I join you guys too?
Of course.
Then you can be the sergeant major
who served in the army his whole life.
Thank you.
My goodness,
we've formed a pretty nifty team.
I'll forget our history and take you in.
Join my team.
We made a pretty good team before,
didn't we?
You're still bluffing?
There are hordes of people out there
looking for you.
Don't kid with me.
No matter how tough you are,
you can't win in here all by yourself.
Don't you see this?
Those masked jerks took away
the beds of those who died.
One mistake, and your bed will be out too.
Worry about your own bed.
Gentlemen.
Don't work with this jerk.
On the outside, he picked his
underlings' pockets for his own benefit.
Then he got bold enough to lay hands
on his boss's pockets,
got caught, and ended up like this.
Know what guys like him
are referred to in my hometown?
A revolutionary asshole.
You commie bitch.
Girls and boys.
Sorry for breaking into this conversation.
What do you want?
Oh, my.
You're very handsome.
Hey, let me join.
Join what?
Your team.
What are you good at?
Everything except for the things I'm not.
I'd be much more useful
than this skinny girl
in many ways.
You're that good?
Should we get it on?
There are empty beds.
Your mealtime begins now.
All players, please come out
-After we eat.
-to the front.
Let me repeat. Your mealtime begins now.
All players,
please form a line in the center.
Those thugs.
Gosh.
Out of 201 players, 187 players returned.
The re-entrance rate is 93%.
Keep an eye on those who didn't return,
and keep me posted.
Yes, sir.
-Geez.
-Gosh.
This brings back old memories.
Did you used to have lunchboxes like this?
Of course.
My wife was always busy every morning,
preparing lunch boxes
for me and my children.
The rice is cold. Geez.
We could've warmed it up
if we had a stove in the middle.
Do you remember?
We had a briquette stove
in our elementary school classroom.
We put our lunch boxes on it,
and it'd get burning hot,
then the rice got scorched too.
-Gi-hun.
-What?
If you have time to reminisce,
try to figure out
what the next game will be.
Hey,
that's not something I can guess.
We'll find out when it begins.
Thinking about what we played so far,
I'm sure it'll be one of the games
kids played way back in the day.
Yes, I think so too.
But there are too many games.
There are Ddakji Game, Dabanggu,
Hopscotch, Biseokchigi, Tag,
Don Katsu, Freeze Tag.
And for girls, Gonggi, Elastics,
and Cat's Cradle.
What else is there?
I don't know how to play any of those.
Don't kids in your country
play these games?
Don't worry.
Kids' games have simple rules.
We'll help you if you don't know.
Thank you.
The work schedule is done for today.
All workers, please return to your rooms.
Let me repeat.
The work schedule is done for today.
All workers, please return to your rooms.
1. ALWAYS WEAR YOUR MASK
OUTSIDE THE ROOM
2. DO NOT CONVERSE
WITHOUT PERMISSION
3. DO NOT LEAVE THE ROOM
Hey, open the door, you jerks!
I really need to pee right now!
Don't you jerks ever take a leak?
Let me use the restroom!
I just need to use the restroom
for one second. Is that so hard?
This room is full of men.
Do you expect me to go on the floor?
Damn it, you scumbags!
At least treat us like humans
if you brought us here to play games!
Hey, Triangle.
I don't need you. Get me your superior.
Get that Square here now, you idiot!
You may not leave the premise
outside of your allotted time.
Shit. Do you think nature calls
only at the time you set for us?
What the…
You freaking bastards!
You don't think
I'll go right here and now?
Damn it.
Hey, I'm going.
Man, you're about to hear a waterfall.
Follow me.
Damn people never listen
until someone screams and shouts.
Damn it.
I have to go too.
What are you doing?
I swept my way to the toilet,
and you sit right on top of it?
Hey.
You're the really annoying type.
You know that?
That rude brat.
Hey.
That's so damn sweet.
You startled me!
What?
Do you want a drag?
Stay there and keep smoking.
What are you doing?
Are you…
going to go in there?
I want a look around.
Buy me some time.
I'll tell you if I find out anything.
Deal.
Step on me.
Gosh.
My constipation is killing me!
I'd rather give birth to a baby!
I'm dying here!
I'm dying. Why won't it come out?
It's time to go back.
Give me just a moment.
It's almost out.
Come on, hurry up and come out.
Hurry up and come out. I've got to hurry!
Come out now.
If you don't, I'm going in.
Wait! No! Wait a second!
There's no toilet paper here!
Darn it.
I'm washing myself with water.
Don't you come in.
Stay right there.
I'm washing myself.
My bottoms are completely naked.
Shit.
Now I'm getting clean.
What are you doing?
Keep stirring.
Come out now.
Damn it, there's no toilet paper!
-If you don't, I'll drag you out.
-I have to wipe myself!
Hey, aren't you supposed to check
each stall for toilet paper?
Get that Square guy here!
I need to file a complaint.
What the hell are you looking at, bastard?
I can't believe this.
You asshole.
Hey, jerk.
Didn't I tell you not to come in?
This is sexual harassment!
Hey, once I get out of here,
I'm going to sue you, bastard.
Damn!
It's now time to go to sleep.
Good work today.
A deserted island, abductions,
surveillance, and the masks.
Hey, what did you see?
What did you see?
I'll tell you tomorrow.
Why tomorrow? Just tell me now.
Hey.
What did you see?
How am I supposed to wait until tomorrow?
A new morning has risen.
Please wake up, everyone.
In ten minutes, head count will begin.
It is now breakfast time.
All players,
please form a line in the center.
Hey.
What did you see?
Tell me now.
You said you'd tell me in the morning.
I'm sure you had time to see something.
Those masked people
were melting something in large pots.
Melt what?
I'm not sure.
Damn it.
I put on that huge show
trying to save your life,
and you're not sure?
I smelled something.
What smell?
Sugar.
You smelled sugar?
So they were melting sugar?
I think so.
That's all you saw?
Listen,
if you're holding back something,
I'm going to burn your eyes out.
I guess I'm hungry.
I'm craving something sweet.
God damn it.
Maybe they're giving us
candied sweet potatoes today.
Starting head count.
Please wait in front of your door.
Head count complete.
All staff, proceed.
Excuse me,
do you have any chocolate milk?
I can't drink regular milk.
I could never digest it
even when I was a kid,
so I never signed up for milk
back in school.
Darn it.
You must have been spanked
by your father a lot when you were young.
How did you know?
My son was just like you.
Sir.
Why aren't you eating that?
You can have it.
Really?
I usually don't eat breakfast.
Thank you, sir.
The smart ones never eat much, you know.
Have this too.
Thank you, sir.
The second game will begin shortly.
Please follow our staff's instructions.
Let me repeat.
The second game will begin shortly.
Please follow our staff's instructions.
You saw something, didn't you?
I heard you talking last night.
Tell me what you saw.
Why should I?
You're a North Korean defector.
All the games they made us play
are the ones I played as a kid.
The next one is likely to be
something similar.
If you tell me,
I could guess what it is.
Why is this playground so big?
What will they make us play?
Welcome to your second game.
Hey, what do you think this is?
Holding out on a roundabout?
Pushing people off of the jungle gym?
Before the second game begins,
Choose one among the four shapes
and stand before it.
What is that?
Circle, triangle,
star, umbrella.
They seem very familiar.
If you tell me, I could guess what it is.
They were melting sugar.
Sang-woo.
What?
What should we do?
I'm not sure.
Choose a shape
and stand in front of it immediately.
Should we move as a team?
That might be dangerous.
We don't know what game it is.
If we all pick the same shape,
we might be in trouble.
Is that so?
There's this saying in investing.
"Don't put all your eggs in one basket."
Sir,
he got into Seoul University
as the top of his class.
He was a famous prodigy
in the neighborhood.
Really? Goodness.
He's an amazing man.
Of course, he is.
Then let's split up as Sang-woo said,
and see how things go.
Who should go where?
I'll take the triangle.
What about you?
Dayira.
-Dayira.
-You mean, circle?
Yes.
It looks like the moon from my hometown.
Then we have the star
and the umbrella left.
You can choose first.
-Should I?
-Yes.
Then I'll take the umbrella.
Umbrella?
Why?
My mom scolded me a lot
because I always lost my umbrellas.
In the end, she only gave me broken ones.
I always wanted to carry
a good umbrella just like the other kids.
You don't want the star?
Do you want to switch?
No, the star sounds great.
We rarely ever get to see stars
in this day and age.
All right, let's get moving.
Once we know what we're playing,
let's come up with a plan together.
Gi-hun.
Yes?
Never mind.
The time to decide has ended.
We will now reveal the game.
All players, please each take a case
in front of you.
Please open the case
and check the contents.
HONEYCOMB
Circle?
The second game is sugar honeycombs.
The shape you have chosen
is the shape you must piece out.
I'm screwed.
The time limit is ten minutes.
You will pass if you trim out the shape
within ten minutes.
Let the game begin.
Wait…
Give me one…
Please. Just one more--
No, I'm sorry.
Please spare my life.
Please--
Player 111, pass.
Player 67, pass.
I did it. The circle.
Circle.
Player 199, pass.
Player 210, pass.
Player 224, pass.
Player 246, pass.
Player 73, pass.
Number 29.
Player 72, pass.
-Yes, sir.
-What's your duty today?
-Player 34, pass.
-My duty is…
Number 29, your duty
is carrying out eliminated players.
Why are you here already?
-I'm sorry.
-Player 44, pass.
I got confused.
Wait here until the game ends.
I'll have a word with you
about that confusion.
Player 32, pass.
Left.
Player 122, pass.
Player 29, pass.
Player 218, pass.
Player 357, pass.
Player 83, pass.
It melted.
This is it. I can melt it from the back.
The lines are thinner,
so it will melt first.
Player 212, pass.
Player 196, pass.
Player 244, pass.
Player 69, pass.
Player 70, pass.
Player 456, pass.
The second game is now over.
All successful players,
please leave the playground immediately.
Move your hands.
Shit.
You assholes!
Damn it.
What kind of a sick game is this?
Why do some get an easy shape
when others are stuck with difficult ones?
Don't come any closer, you assholes!
I'll kill this bastard.
I'll really kill him.
Take your mask off.
Mask off, now!
Turn around.
Such a young kid…
How did you end up like this?
Remember.
Once they find out who you are,
you're dead.
Number 29.
Wait here until the game ends.
I'll have a word with you
about that confusion.
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon