What are you looking at?
What should we do about the game?
Proceed.
Sir.
Thank you.
You look great.
The fourth game will begin momentarily.
All players, follow staff's instructions
and proceed to the game hall.
Let me repeat.
The fourth game will begin.
All players, follow staff's instructions
and proceed to the game hall.
What you are witnessing right now
are the ones who broke the rules
of this world for their benefit and
tainted the pure ideology of this world.
Each and every one of you is
considered equal in this world.
You must be guaranteed equal opportunity
without any discrimination.
We promise not to let
such an unfortunate incident be repeated.
We truly apologize for this tragedy.
EPISODE 6
GGANBU
LIST OF WINNERS
NON-DISCLOSURE AGREEMENT
Your face looks awful.
Why? Is your connection gone?
That darned wench.
Welcome to your fourth game.
This game will be played in teams of two.
Find someone
you wish to play the game with.
When two people agree to play as a team
and shake hands, you become partners.
Let me repeat.
This game will be played in teams of two.
Find someone
you wish to play the game with.
When two people agree to play as a team
and shake hands, you become partners.
Please form teams of two
within ten minutes.
Hey, babe.
Team up with me.
I'm better than you'd expect.
And I'm stronger than most men.
And I've been convicted
of fraud five times.
I never bothered to study,
but I'm unbelievably smart.
If you play with me,
I'll do anything you tell me.
You'll be shocked to find out
the things I can do for you.
Please?
You're being hesitant although you all
want to play with me, aren't you?
Why? Can't decide?
Should I decide for you all?
Stop embarrassing yourself.
That won't get anyone to play with you.
Just be honest.
You don't want a woman or an old man
as your partner.
Of course not. Our lives are at stake.
We almost died playing Tug-of-War.
You're right.
There's a reason why
God created Eve from Adam's rib.
Men and women play
different roles and parts.
You idiots.
This isn't the Garden of Eden.
Hey, where are you going?
Why? Do you want to team up with me?
You idiots.
You're making a big mistake
by not teaming up with me.
-Sang-woo, play with--
-Ali, play with me.
You just need to be either strong or smart
for most of the games here.
If we team up,
we can win against most teams.
No, don't mind me.
It's okay. Really. It's okay.
You two will make a great team.
I'll find someone else.
Let's make this work.
Well…
Sir.
I'm sorry, but…
You need to put this on.
People will look down on you
if you aren't wearing your jacket.
Let's do this.
My service to you, Boss.
Hey.
Team up with me.
Why should I?
Then will you beg those boomers
to play with you?
How embarrassing.
I don't care if it's embarrassing.
I have to win no matter what.
Then team up with me.
I'll make sure you win.
How will you do that?
Whatever it takes.
Why do you want to team up with me?
Why did you ask me to join you?
You were the only one
who looked like who'd come along.
I feel the same way now.
You won't find anyone better than me
among those who are left.
On the outside, I'm a math teacher
and I play soccer in the morning,
so I'm fit.
Many others wanted to play with me,
but I turned them down for you.
I thought we'd make a great team.
The thing is…
we don't know what we're going to play.
Stop shopping around
and just team up with me.
At this rate, you'll fail to team up
with anyone and get left behind.
You know,
the cheater was executed,
so there are only 39 left.
Once everyone teams up in pairs,
one will be left behind.
Then what will happen?
What do you think?
They'll be eliminated, obviously.
I'm guessing it'll be that old man.
Stop dragging this on
and be my partner.
Sir.
Will you team up with me?
The time for finding a partner is over.
-You're all making a big mistake.
-All players, proceed
-to the game hall with your partner.
-Do you think you can win without me?
I'm Han Mi-nyeo!
I totally owned everyone
from Dongducheon to Gangnam!
Darn it.
What if you have to play
Gonggi or Elastics?
I'm an expert in those.
So babe, please play with me.
Boys aren't very good at those.
Babe!
Hey, you can be my partner.
Tell everyone with a dick to get lost.
-What's wrong with you?
-We girls should stick together!
-My gosh!
-I'm good with women too!
I'll be really good!
Stop it!
-Hey, don't trust this jerk.
-Okay, sure.
This jerk is a scumbag.
He'll abandon you anytime.
He was in league
with that dead doctor out there.
-All right.
-Did you know that?
He wanted to save his own ass,
so he kept it a secret from you.
Tell me if I'm wrong, you jerk!
He was with them too!
-Hey.
-He deserves to die too!
Get the hell off!
Where is everyone?
Why is everyone gone?
I don't have a partner yet.
Where's my partner?
Who took my partner away?
Where's my partner, you jerks?
Where's my partner?
Bring my partner here! You jerks!
My partner!
What an annoying bitch.
I'm glad I won't have to see her again.
By the way,
what was she saying earlier?
About you with that doctor…
Forget about it.
That bitch was desperate
and said whatever came to mind.
All players, follow the
staff's instructions to your positions.
Ali, don't be nervous.
We'll surely win if we work together.
Now that I'm working with you,
I feel like we could win.
Yes, let's win and get out of here.
We'll take the money
and go back to our families.
Okay, Sang-woo.
I used to live
in a neighborhood just like this one.
Me too.
I lived in an alley very similar
to this one as a kid.
Please take one pouch each.
There are ten marbles in each pouch.
Please check how many there are.
Sir, I think we're playing Marbles.
You've played this before, right?
Of course, I have.
I used to play Marbles very often
back when I was little.
I was pretty good.
I'm not so bad myself.
What a relief.
-I was worried it might require strength.
-Good.
In that case, we need to make a pact
and become gganbu.
Gganbu?
I thought you played Marbles a lot.
How could you not know what gganbu is?
It's a friend in the neighborhood
who you share your marbles
and ddakji and everything with.
Yes, that gganbu. I remember now.
I had one in my town too.
-He was my best friend.
-Yes, that gganbu.
Did we do this to make the pact?
You're right. This is it.
-Sir. No, my gganbu.
-Yes?
Let's sweep all the marbles
in this neighborhood.
In this game, using your ten marbles,
you will compete with your partner.
The player who takes all ten marbles
from your partner wins.
Let me repeat.
Using your ten marbles,
you will compete with your partner.
The player who takes all ten marbles
from your partner wins.
Honey.
Damn it.
Sang-woo.
How pretty.
Sir.
You have 30 minutes.
Let the games begin.
Sir.
Let's do this.
That means one of us will die.
Then do you want to stand around
and die together?
Or will you die on my behalf?
You haven't played this, right?
This is the biggest tragedy
since the Korean War.
Right?
What should we play?
You're so cold.
As cold as ice.
Are you really a spy from the North?
Stop talking nonsense.
Tell me what game to play.
I have no idea either.
This is what those boomers
used to play as kids.
They said we're free
to create our own rules.
I'll give it some thought.
It was definitely
somewhere around here.
Sir, we have to play this game right now.
This is weird.
It's definitely this alley.
Where did my house go?
Sir.
You just have to guess
if the number of marbles I'm holding
is odd or even.
Odd or even?
What's that?
Odd numbers like one, three, and five.
Even numbers are two, four, and six.
Do you get it?
Give it a good thought
and bet your marbles on either one.
Odd.
How many did you bet?
Darn it.
I should've bet one more.
Stop giggling, asshole.
Damn it, why are you swearing at me?
Do you really think I'm your minion
just because I kept calling you Boss?
Do you want to die, asshole?
Kill me? And how are you going to do that?
You can't resort to violence,
you half-witted idiot.
Sir, we really have to play now.
What?
Marbles!
Marbles?
See? Everyone else is doing it.
We have to do this too.
No.
Do you think I'm a kid?
Wait. Sir!
Let's…
end the game in one round.
Let's bet everything
and just play one round.
Do you want to do that
for the entire remaining time?
Yes! Nice.
Damn it.
Two, three, four.
My turn.
Fine. What are we playing?
Why are you in such a hurry?
Are you dying to kill me?
We're playing just one round.
We have some time left.
Let's do it last minute.
Then what are we going to do until then?
Let's talk.
Talk about what?
Things we couldn't tell other people.
One of us is going to die here anyway.
No matter what we tell each other,
there's no reason to feel embarrassed.
Don't you think?
Even.
How many did you bet?
Two.
Your turn.
I don't want to do this with you.
Sir.
I want to play with someone else.
Stop talking nonsense
and grab the marbles.
That man has dementia.
He's not in his right mind.
Isn't it like he's given up?
Since he can't play this game. No?
Darn it.
Let's play it just this once.
This is really…
It's a lot of fun.
I want to go home.
I'm sure my home is
somewhere in this alley.
Damn it!
Will you please pull yourself together?
If we stay like this, we'll both die!
You probably don't care
since you have the tumor in your head,
but I have to get out of here alive.
I have to stay alive
and get the heck out of here!
Stop yelling at me.
I'll play with you.
And 12, 13, 14, 15. All right!
Shit, change the game.
Why should I? I'm on a roll.
We played this
the way you wanted until now,
so now we're playing what I want.
I don't want to.
Damn it.
Let us change the game. That's only fair.
You people said everyone is equal here,
didn't you?
Request accepted.
What do you want to play?
Even.
What are you doing? Open your hand.
You bastard.
You're cheating, aren't you?
Sang-woo, what are you talking about?
How come you keep winning?
The odds of winning are 50-50.
This situation makes absolutely no sense!
No, I didn't do anything.
You jerk. You deceived me
pretending to know nothing about it!
You said you've never done this before!
What did you do? Tell me!
Why did you come here from the North?
I thought it'd be better here.
So?
Is it better?
What about your family?
Are they here with you?
Just my younger brother.
What about your parents?
My dad was shot while crossing the river,
then drifted down.
My mom…
was caught by the public security officers
in China, then sent back.
Where's your brother?
At a children's home.
Even.
Odd. Even. Odd. Even.
Did I win?
How many did you bet?
Darn.
We'll take turns throwing marbles
until one of us gets it into that hole.
If I make it?
Then you get to take
all the marbles on the ground.
So you want a chance
to turn the game around at once.
What's wrong? Are you scared?
Shit. I'm not scared.
I'm not so bad when it comes
to putting things into holes.
Are you okay with that?
If you leave here with that money,
what will you do with it?
I'll buy a house to live with my brother,
then bring my mom from the North.
Hey, you can do that and much more
with 40 billion won.
Anything else?
Is there anywhere you want to go?
Jeju Island.
Jeju Island?
I saw it on TV.
It looked exotic and nothing like Korea.
Hey,
you've got to dream big, don't you think?
You should at least go to Hawaii,
no, the Maldives.
And have a glass of mojito too.
Mojito?
Haven't you seen that movie?
The one with Lee Byung-hun.
"Go to mojito
and have a glass of Maldives."
Don't you know?
Hey, that's no good.
Once we get out of here,
I should teach you how people splurge
in the South.
We can't get out of here together.
I'm sorry, Ali.
I took you wrong.
But I can't die like this.
If I die here,
my entire family will die too.
I'm sorry, Sang-woo.
I'm so sorry,
but I have a family too.
Hey, Ali.
If you help me,
there's a way both of us could live.
You got this far all thanks to me.
I gave you the bus fare,
my plan helped you survive the Tug-of-War,
we kept watch at night together,
and just before the game, we promised
to leave here together, didn't we?
So, please.
Please trust me this once and help me.
Please?
What's your plan?
Could it be
odd?
It might be even.
-It must be even.
-Hurry up and say it.
Odd.
I won again.
How many did you bet?
Darn it.
I have one.
I still have one left.
Darn it.
My guess is that
some of the teams won't be able
to decide the winner in time.
Why not?
Do you remember the rule?
The person who wins their partner's
marbles in 30 minutes passes.
So think about it.
Not all of the teams will end up
with one winner.
They win, lose, go back and forth.
I'm sure there will be
teams without any winners.
What will they do?
Eliminate all those teams?
That makes no sense.
They must decide the winner. Right?
Yes.
When that happens,
I'm sure they'll let us play in teams.
A team will add up their marbles
and play against other teams
with 20 marbles.
We can play as a team
just as we planned from the start.
We can leave this place together.
Player 414, eliminated.
Do you want
to do that to me?
Player 2, eliminated.
Have you ever seen a dead person
before you came here?
A plague broke out in my town
when I was a kid.
People died day after day.
Soldiers piled up the bodies
and burned them.
That's when my grandma, grandpa,
and older brother
all burned up.
I got to say,
your stories are way too dark.
You?
What about you?
Player 130, eliminated.
The first one I saw
was my mom.
One day coming back from school,
I found her dead on the floor at home.
And next to her
was my so-called dad
with a knife in his hand.
The next dead person I saw…
was my dad.
And the one standing
next to him with a knife
was me.
He was a pastor.
Whenever he beat my mom
and did the unthinkable to me,
he always prayed
that our sins be forgiven.
But he didn't pray
the day he killed my mom.
Maybe he knew he couldn't be forgiven.
Player 40, eliminated.
Even.
No, wait.
One second.
Wait, hold on.
Odd.
What did you just say?
What?
What…
did you just say?
Even…
I said even.
That means
I lost.
Are you sure we can both win?
Really?
Hear me out first and turn me down
if you don't like the plan.
If you do that,
I'll just give you my last marble.
So you won't feel guilty about killing me.
What's
your plan?
Player 68, eliminated.
It depends on who we'll be up against.
We have to find out
which teams will end up left.
We don't have much time, so let's split up
and see how other teams are doing.
Find teams that seem
very young or very old
among the ones who are still playing.
Their age?
Yes, that's what's important.
Find out if they're young like you
or if they're over 50.
You take the alley across the street.
I'll go the other way.
Okay, Sang-woo.
Ali.
Your bag.
It's dangerous carrying it like that.
Everyone will go crazy at the last minute.
Who knows what'll happen?
We're doomed if you lose this.
You know that, right?
I'll make it safe for you.
What will you do
if you leave here with the money?
I haven't thought about it.
Someone was waiting for me
when I was released from prison.
I thought he was a creditor
who came to collect my dad's debt.
But he gave me a business card.
That weird card.
I just came
because I had nowhere else to go.
So I haven't thought about
what to do if I get out.
Should we go to Jeju together?
Sorry.
My mistake, again.
Player 229, eliminated.
Damn it.
Shit.
I thought it'd go in. Damn it.
You have nothing left now?
I still have
one left.
Deok-su.
It was fun while it lasted.
It went in. That's mine! My blue marble!
It was fun while it lasted, asshole.
Shit!
You bastards!
Player 278, eliminated.
Here.
What do you think?
Doesn't it seem much safer?
Yes.
Then we'll meet here again
when the timer hits three minutes.
I'll tell you my plan then.
Odd.
One, two, three.
We both have three marbles.
Yes, but what did you just say?
What?
What did I say?
You said it's even.
Did I
say that?
Yes.
That means
I lost again.
Player 43, eliminated.
A team of older people.
Player 85, eliminated.
Just throw it already.
Three youngsters.
-I can't believe I missed it!
-Get out of the way.
Two old people.
Player 276, eliminated.
It's your turn.
What?
Right.
Here.
Odd.
What's the date today?
The 24th of this month
is my son's birthday.
I was going to buy him a toy robot
for his birthday.
But I completely forgot
and didn't get him anything last year.
I have to get him something this time.
Right.
What did you say?
Odd.
I have 20 marbles.
The rule you said
was to obtain my opponent's marbles
while playing any games
without using any violence.
And I never resorted to any violence.
How many? Two left?
Darn it.
You have three minutes until the game
is over. You have three minutes.
Player 158, eliminated.
Let's do it.
Whoever throws a marble
closer to that wall wins.
What do you think?
It's Sae-byeok.
What is?
My name.
Kang Sae-byeok.
Sae-byeok.
Nice name.
What about you?
Ji-yeong.
Family name?
I don't have one.
Who should go first?
You can go first.
Your number is before mine too.
All of my marbles are gone.
What should I do?
I'd love to play more.
Can you let me
borrow just one marble?
I'm sorry.
Player 70, eliminated.
Look at this.
I have one marble left.
There was one left.
Two, four, six, eight,
two, four, six, eight. Nineteen.
Nineteen.
No. Sir, wait.
Sir!
What are you doing?
I lost.
What do you think you're doing?
That marble just slipped.
Is this what you meant
by making sure I'll win?
Do you think I'll be thankful?
Throw it again.
Even if I did,
I wouldn't be able to win anyway.
Just let me lose in style.
Stop acting cool and just throw it again!
I don't have anything.
What?
You have a reason to leave this place,
but I don't.
I've been thinking about what I should do
once I get out since you asked me.
But no matter how much I think,
I can't think of one.
Someone who has a good reason
should leave.
That's the right thing.
Make sure you leave this place alive.
And…
meet your mom,
bring your brother back,
and go to Jeju Island too.
Sang-woo.
Sang-woo, where are you?
Sang-woo. Sang-woo!
I checked everyone.
Sang-woo!
Player 199, eliminated.
Kang Sae-byeok!
Thanks
for playing with me.
Player 240, eliminated.
Sir, let's play just one more time.
Please, one more round.
Darn it.
It's this house.
I used to live in this house
with my wife and son.
I had a small pond in the front yard too.
Sir, you have one marble left.
You have to play that game with me.
When I'd come home from work,
my son would be having so much fun
with his friends.
He didn't even realize I'd come home.
Pull yourself together!
Pull yourself together and listen to me!
Then I'd hide behind that utility pole
and take a peek at him playing.
They were having so much fun.
Please.
Please pull yourself together.
I beg you, please.
Why don't we play one more round
betting everything we have?
What?
I'll bet everything I have.
You bet everything you have too.
What do you mean?
We're going to bet everything you have
and everything I have.
That's only fair.
Are you telling me to bet everything
to get that one marble?
What kind of nonsense is this?
That makes no sense!
Then…
does fooling me
and taking my marbles make sense?
Take it.
It's yours.
We're…
gganbu, aren't we?
Don't you remember?
We made a pinky promise
to be each other's gganbu.
And when you're gganbu with another,
you share everything.
Thank you
for everything.
Thanks to you,
I had a good time
before I go.
It's all right.
Everything
will be all right.
I remember my name now.
My name is Il-nam.
Oh Il-nam.
Player 1, eliminated.
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon