My town called that game "the Squid Game".
It was named so because the game
was played in a squid-like outline.
The rules are simple.
Children are divided into two groups,
the offense and the defense.
Once the game starts, the defense
can run around on two feet within bounds,
while the offense outside the line
is only allowed to hop on one foot.
Your mom!
But if an attacker cuts through the waist
of the squid outpacing the defense,
he or she is given the freedom
to walk freely on two feet.
The secret inspector.
For whatever reason,
we called that the secret inspector.
After preparing for the final battle,
the attackers gather
at the entrance of the squid.
Go.
In order to win, the attackers
must tap the small closed-off
space on the squid's head with their foot.
If the defender pushes you
out of the squid's line,
you die.
That's right. You die.
Hooray!
"Hooray."
Once you take the winning tap,
you yell out, "Hooray."
And, in that moment,
I felt as if I owned the entire world,
exhilarated.
EPISODE 1
RED LIGHT, GREEN LIGHT
What's this? Is it for me?
Do you remember that
it's Ga-yeong's birthday today?
Yes, I do.
Don't forget and go buy her dinner later.
You can't eat anything nice
with this these days.
Ga-yeong loves fried chicken, you know.
Go buy her some fried chicken.
I can't just get her chicken.
I should get her a birthday gift.
Give me a little more.
I got no money.
What are you talking about?
I gave you all the money I made
as a chauffeur.
Goodness, that petty change?
Hey, that's not even enough to pay off
the monthly interest for your loan.
We can't pay it off
by living like this anyway,
so let's use some when we have to.
Goodness.
And will you please stop doing that?
Soak the dishes in water
after you're done.
You always say your back is in pain,
and you don't even make much!
Let's see…
DAEHAN BANK
ENTER YOUR PIN
INCORRECT PIN
My birthday should be it.
She changed the pin.
Your mom finally disowned you.
Darn it.
INCORRECT PIN
What did that old woman change it to?
Try her birthday or something.
Her birthday?
Mom's birthday…
You don't know your mom's birthday?
You ungrateful bastard!
Piss off, moron! I know!
She celebrates by the lunar calendar,
so it changes every year.
Idiot. You don't know anything…
Try the lunar date then.
Damn it.
God damn it!
Darn it.
Hey. Watch it.
The card will be blocked
if you get it wrong again.
Think hard. Got anything else?
Checking-- Please press the amount
you would like to withdraw.
What was it? What did you use?
Today. My daughter's birthday.
Man, the old woman cares
for her granddaughter more than me.
My gosh.
No. 9 Triple Line is in second.
No. 6 Dry Thunder is in third.
No. 3 Jack Prince is in fourth.
And the gap with the lead is widening.
Out of the straight course
and into the turn,
-Yes, that's it. Number nine!
-Whip it! Whip!
-No. 3 Jack Prince is accelerating
-Whip! Whip!
-and catching up to No. 9 Triple Line.
-Let's go! Come on!
-No. 4 Hwarang is not giving up his place.
-Whip it! Run!
-No. 4 Hwarang crosses the finish line.
-No, no!
Damn it!
You said number nine would definitely win!
That stupid idiot.
How could you lose
with such a great horse?
Betting for the tenth race
is about to end.
-I repeat.
-Hurry it up, will you?
Betting for the tenth race
is about to end.
Hey.
-What are you--
-Will you just leave me the heck alone?
I'm trying to think!
All right.
No. 9 Baekil Legend
is placed right in the middle.
-No. 6 Thunderflash is quickly
-Okay.
-catching up to the frontrunners,
-Good, keep going.
-but the gap is still wide.
-Run!
-They're heading into the curve again.
-Okay. Turn.
-No. 7 Golden Bullet and No. 8 Mad Dash.
-Yes, turn.
-They're going full speed.
-Stick to them! Outside!
But, wait! Wrapping around the outside…
-It's No. 6 Thunderflash!
-Yes!
-And he continues to gain ground!
-Six and eight, go!
-The gap is closing!
-Whip! Whip it!
-No. 6 has taken the second-place spot,
-Go! Go!
-and he's not stopping there.
-He's taken the lead!
-Go! Go!
-No. 6 Thunderflash brings it home!
-Yes!
Come to me! Six and eight!
I got it!
-Where did six come from?
-Man, seriously!
What did I say?
I said it's my daughter's birthday today!
June 8. So, 6 and 8!
Here's 4,560,000 won.
Thank you.
Here.
Buy yourself a cup of Americano.
What about me?
-My mom's money pulled through!
-Wait for me, buddy!
Where's the ATM?
OFF TRACK BETTING
Daddy will pick you up
in front of your academy.
What? Fried chicken?
Hey, feel free to choose
something more expensive.
Write down everything you want to eat.
No.
Don't write it down during class.
Do it during break time. Okay?
All right. Seven o'clock.
Guess what I'll get you for your birthday.
You can look forward to it.
You'll be surprised…
Hey, Gi-hun!
Hey!
Long time no see!
Hey, Ga-yeong. I love you, too.
-What?
-Hey, get him!
Excuse me. Coming through!
I'm sorry. Kid, are you okay?
Goodness.
-I'm sorry.
-Grab him!
Hey! Stop right there!
Wait. One second. Let me stand up.
I have money. I really do.
Do you?
Then why did you run?
That's because…
I wanted to pay you all at once
to save you the trouble.
Goodness, what a trooper.
So? How much do you have?
Four million.
Please take this for now,
and I'll pay the rest next month…
Kid, are you okay?
Let me see.
Come on, let me see.
Goodness.
That's sweet.
You must've had lots of good food
with my money.
I had money on me.
Just now, six and eight…
Six and eight won earlier, so I had money.
Hey.
Do you know why
it's so easy to get nosebleeds?
Because there are
a lot of capillary vessels in there.
No, please. Please don't kill me.
Your blood was tasty.
Maybe I'll take a bowl
and cook up some blood soup tonight.
I'll pay you back.
I really mean it. I'll pay up.
Man, you punk.
Don't cry. You're making me feel bad.
How did he know I was a softie?
Hey.
Now, wipe your tears
and stamp your fingerprint.
If you don't pay up by next month,
I'm taking one of your kidneys here
and one of these eyes instead.
You don't like it?
That's not it. Yes, I understand.
-Here.
-Okay.
Well, I need an ink pad.
There it is. All-natural ink pad.
Sorry?
Right, yes.
Yes, right there. Good.
DISCLAIMER OF PHYSICAL RIGHTS
Great job.
You have a month. Take care of yourself.
Wait, sir.
Well, I'm sorry but…
may I borrow 10,000 won?
Seriously, you little…
WINDOW CLOSED
Excuse me.
I'm sorry,
could I have that 10,000 won back?
THE FUN DOESN'T END, CRANE GAME
Darn it.
Come on!
Okay. That's it.
Damn!
God damn it!
Sir,
you keep failing
because you pick without thinking.
Are you any good?
That's it. Good.
Yes, that's it.
Great job! Great work!
This?
I was bitten by a huge mosquito.
Mosquitoes are really mean these days.
Dad, you're free to get into fights,
but don't get beaten up.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
I wanted to buy you
something more delicious.
It's okay.
I went to a steakhouse
with Mom and my stepdad.
You had steak?
I see.
But I think tteokbokki is way better.
Mom won't let me have this
saying it's junk food.
Eat up.
Right!
Ga-yeong, I got you a birthday present.
Did you know there are a lot of women
in the army these days?
There won't be any discrimination
between men and women in your future.
You need to get used to these things.
It's even has a light.
Hey, it looks like the real deal,
doesn't it?
But I think you'll get in trouble again
if Mom sees this.
Is that so?
Then I'll keep this until you get older.
But don't use that to smoke.
I quit smoking.
All right.
I'll be sure to quit smoking.
And on your next birthday,
I'll get you a really awesome present.
I promise, Ga-yeong.
Next year?
Think of your birthday last year.
It came around quickly, right?
The next one will come around
in a flash too.
Dad.
Yes? What is it?
Never mind.
All right. Have some more tteokbokki.
Excuse me,
we'll have 1,000 won's worth more.
Mix in a lot of fish cake.
Why did you bring her back so late?
She's dressed lightly.
She got sleepy, so I had to carry her.
We're only ten minutes late.
I said I'd drive to pick her up.
That's enough. It's her birthday.
Mom.
-There, there.
-Ga-yeong, come down.
I'll carry her to the elevator.
She'll catch a bad habit.
Mom…
-Ga-yeong, come down.
-My gosh. Seriously.
Come on. Let's go.
Bye, Dad.
Go on in.
Wait a minute! Wait…
Sir.
Do you have a minute?
I don't believe in Jesus.
It's not that.
I'd like to give you a great opportunity--
I come from a Buddhist household,
so stop bothering me and get lost.
Sir.
Would you like to play a game with me?
What are you?
A solicitor?
You people have
all kinds of sales tactics.
I can see how unfortunate
your situation is,
but I have no time to…
Sir, you've played ddakji before,
haven't you?
Play ddakji with me. Each time you win,
I will give you 100,000 won.
Wait, so if I flip your ddakji over,
you'll give me 100,000 won?
However, each time I win,
you must give me 100,000 won.
I'll let you go first.
I'm in a really foul mood today.
If this is some kind of scam,
I'm going to kill you today.
I'll go first, then.
Which color do you want?
Do you not have any money?
Money…
You can use your body to pay up.
My body?
What's with you?
I'll take off 100,000 won per slap.
One more round.
The doors are opening.
Another round!
I won! See that?
Did you see that? I won!
Come here. Get your face over here.
Let go of this, you jerk.
Here's your 100,000 won.
Congratulations.
Right.
I get 100,000 won.
Sir.
You can make a lot
by playing such games for a few days.
Would you like to give it a try?
Hey, man.
Is this some sort of new pyramid scheme?
But you got the wrong man.
I'm not that naive.
Mr. Seong Gi-hun.
You signed a disclaimer
of physical rights today, didn't you?
Name, Seong Gi-hun. 47 years old.
Education level,
Daehan Technical High School.
Former employee of Dragon Motors,
Assembly Team One.
Resigned ten years ago
during restructuring.
Opened a chicken restaurant
and a snack bar, both failed.
Currently working as a chauffeur.
Has a ten-year-old girl with an ex-wife,
divorced three years ago.
As of now,
you owe 160 million won to loan sharks
and 255 million won to the bank.
Who are you?
How dare you run a background check on me?
We don't have many spots left.
Give me a call.
All right. Whatever.
Thirsty in the middle of the night
I open the fridge
Did you have a drink today?
No.
I haven't had a drop of alcohol,
but I feel tipsy.
Because I made money today!
Gi-hun, do you still gamble?
I didn't gamble.
I earned this money fair and square.
What's with your face by the way?
-Do you get into fights now?
-Hey, forget it.
I wonder what Sang-woo is up to now.
How's he doing at work?
He's always busy.
He's abroad right now on a business trip.
That ungrateful punk.
Tell him to call me when he comes home.
You remember, right?
He got into Seoul National University
thanks to me.
I used to take him to school
when we were kids.
He got into college and got a job
because of me,
but he's never bought me a drink.
Stop talking nonsense.
Take this and go home.
Don't go to a bar. Go straight home.
Here. Keep the change.
Thirsty in the middle of the night
I open the fridge
That's worth 12,000 won, you rascal.
A salted mackerel
In the corner of the room
Are you hungry? Are you?
Here.
Eat this.
You have to finish it, okay?
I bought that with the money I made
by getting slapped.
I am quite the fool
Just looking at my mom pleases me
Here. It's an allowance.
Take it.
Goodness.
Did you gamble again?
I didn't.
Then, what happened to your face?
Why aren't you answering?
It's nothing like that!
Wait, did you steal this from someone?
I didn't gamble or steal.
I worked my hands, face, and body off
to earn this money.
My gosh.
Did you buy fried chicken for Ga-yeong?
I bought her dinner
and a birthday present before I came home.
Did she tell you anything?
Tell me what?
Ga-yeong, her mother, and her stepdad
are all moving to the US next year.
And on your next birthday,
I'll get you a really awesome present.
I promise, Ga-yeong.
Next year?
The US?
Yes.
Her stepdad got a new job in the US,
so the entire family is moving there.
I see.
How can you eat anything right now?
You need to get your daughter back.
How am I going to do that?
That was settled
when we signed the divorce papers.
The young man upstairs
who's well-versed in the law said
if the father can prove
he can financially support his child,
he can take the child back.
If she moves to the US,
she'll forget how to speak Korean,
then it'll be hard for you two
to talk to each other.
You'll become a stranger to her for good.
Are you sure
you can live without seeing her?
Hello.
I'm…
the guy who got
your business card this afternoon.
Do you wish to participate in the game?
If you wish to participate,
please state your name and birthdate.
Gosh.
Mr. Seong Gi-hun?
Yes.
The password?
Red light, green light.
I guess everyone is…
tired.
How long will it take
to get to the game venue?
What?
Fifty, fifty-two…
fifty-five, fifty-six…
Sir.
What are you doing?
Don't talk to me. You're distracting me.
Fifty… what was it?
Are you counting the number of people?
Yes, so stop talking to me.
And then… What?
Wait.
Where was I?
Sir, look over there.
There are 456 people here.
Wait, you were the first to get here.
And I'm… What?
I'm last.
I know that too.
I'm just counting the numbers.
My doctor said counting numbers
is good for preventing dementia.
Why did you come here when you're
old enough to worry about dementia?
You should be eating meals
your daughter-in-law makes for you,
then lying down on the warm floor
watching your grandkids acting cute.
What about your parents?
Do they get to eat fresh-cooked meals
their daughter-in-law makes for them?
You see, my days are numbered.
Sorry?
My doctor said
there's a lump in my head.
A lump?
Brain tumor.
You bitch!
Hey!
Geez.
I can't believe I've run into you here.
Look at those eyes.
Your temper hasn't changed.
Then again,
you're not the type
to back down after a few blows.
I fed you, put a roof over your head,
even taught you my skills,
but you backstab me?
You already took more from me
than what I owe you.
If that's true, why did you run away?
I didn't run away.
I just went independent.
"Independent"?
You went independent?
Are you Yu Gwan-sun or what?
Go out and wave a flag, then.
Oh, right.
You're from the North,
so wave the North Korean flag.
Come here.
That scar on your neck.
Yes, it's you, the pickpocket!
Give me my money back. Where's my money?
Give it back!
What the hell?
Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
Me? Well…
I'm Seong Gi-hun from Ssangmun-dong.
Hey, Mr. Ssangmun-dong.
Yes?
I'm not done with this wench.
I'm sorry, but I also have
something urgent to discuss
with this sister over here.
You bastard.
What's your relation with her?
My gosh.
Then what's your relation with her?
You obviously look like a thug
who preys on girls like her.
Did you tell her to steal my money?
-You son of a bitch!
-Wait!
This thug is trying to kill me!
Someone get over here! We need help!
There they are.
Over here! We got a thug and a pickpocket.
A thug and a pickpocket.
I would like to extend
a hearty welcome to you all.
Everyone here will participate
in six different games over six days.
Those who win all six games
will get a handsome cash prize.
How are we supposed to believe you?
You suddenly put us to sleep,
take our phones and wallets away,
then bring us to this mysterious place.
Now you show up saying you'll pay us
handsomely for playing a few games?
Do you expect us to believe that?
We reluctantly took those measures
to maintain our confidentiality
bringing you here.
We'll return everything
once the games are over.
How come you are wearing those masks?
We do not disclose the faces
and personal information of our staff
to the participants.
It's a measure we take
for the fairness of games and privacy.
-Please understand.
-I don't trust a word you just said.
You lured, kidnapped, and locked us up.
You make all kinds of excuses
to keep yourself hidden
after all those illegal actions.
Give us one good reason
why we should trust you.
Player 218, Cho Sang-woo.
Age, 46.
Former team leader
of Team Two at Joy Investments.
Siphoned money from his clients,
then invested in derivatives
and futures options with it and failed.
Current loss, 650 million won.
Player 107, Kim Mi-ok,
540 million won in debt.
Player 118, Oh Yeong-uk,
1.02 billion won in debt.
Player 322, Jung Min-tae,
880 million won in debt.
Player 119, No Sang-hun,
1.39 billion won in debt.
Player 369, Park Ju-un,
900 million won in debt.
All of you in this room
are living on the edge,
with debts you just can't pay off.
When we first went to see you,
none of you trusted us.
But as you know, we played a game
and gave you money as promised.
So everyone here trusted us
and volunteered to participate in
this game of your own free will.
I'll give you one last chance to choose.
Will you go back to living your lousy life
being chased by your creditors?
Or will you grab the last opportunity
we're offering here?
What kind of games are we playing?
In order to play fair,
we cannot disclose any information
on the games ahead of time.
Excuse me.
Just how much is the prize money?
Your prize money will be accumulated
in the piggy bank after every game.
We will disclose the amount to everyone
after the first game is over.
If you do not wish to participate,
please let us know now.
PLAYER CONSENT FORM
CLAUSE 1: A PLAYER IS NOT ALLOWED
TO STOP PLAYING
CLAUSE 2: A PLAYER WHO REFUSES TO PLAY
WILL BE ELIMINATED
CLAUSE 3: GAMES MAY BE TERMINATED
IF THE MAJORITY AGREES
Is this all?
SIGNATURE, SEONG GI-HUN
The game is about to begin.
All players, follow the staff's
instructions and proceed to the game hall.
Hey, look over there.
Damn, this place is freaking huge.
Please look into the camera.
Darn it.
Move, idiot.
Please look into the camera.
Verified.
Hey, Sang-woo!
It is you, Sang-woo.
What happened? Why are you here?
I went to your mom's store recently,
and she said you were abroad
on a business trip.
And is what he said true?
You're in debt?
Cho Sang-woo who attends SNU,
the pride of Ssangmun-dong?
Welcome to the first game.
Let's talk later.
All players,
please wait a moment on the field.
Let me repeat.
All players,
please wait a moment on the field.
-Hey.
-What?
Look over there. What is that?
It looks really freaky.
Damn, that thing has a freaking huge head.
The first game is Red Light, Green Light.
You can move forward while
"it" shouts out, "Green Light, Red Light"
If your movement is detected afterward,
you will be eliminated.
Red Light, Green Light?
The game we played as kids?
-Let me repeat.
-I think so.
-Is this a fucking joke?
-You can move forward
-Are they serious?
-while "it" shouts out,
-Want to bet who finishes first?
-"Green Light, Red Light."
If your movement is detected afterward,
you will be eliminated.
A million won.
Deal?
Man, damn it.
Deal.
Those who cross the finish line
without getting caught in five minutes
pass this round.
Then let the game begin.
Green Light, Red Light.
Player 324. Eliminated.
That idiot got caught.
What…
was that sound?
Green Light, Red Light.
Hey, you're eliminated, you idiot.
Stop putting on a show and get up.
Let me repeat.
You can move forward while
"it" shouts out, "Green Light, Red Light."
If your movement is detected afterward,
you will be eliminated.
Let me repeat.
You can move forward while
"it" shouts out, "Green Light, Red Light."
If your movement is detected afterward,
you will be eliminated.
Let the game begin.
Green Light, Red Light.
Gi-hun, don't turn your head. Just listen.
You'll die if you stay like that.
I think that doll is a motion sensor.
You won't be caught
if you hide behind someone.
Green Light, Red Light.
There's no time.
Who is that behind me all along?
The one who backstabbed you.
You bitch.
Want me to stab you in the back again?
No, don't.
Please.
Stop trembling, moron.
You'll die if you get caught.
Green Light, Red Light.
Please, help me. Please.
Let me go.
Please…
Green Light, Red Light.
Subtitle translation by: Eun-sook Yoon